I don't fight anymore. The last time I
got in a fight, I was like uh it was
like 10 years ago. [clears throat] I was
living in New York City and I was
walking in my neighborhood like in the
the Lower East Side and I I hear this
guy behind ME GOES, "HEY MAN, WHAT ARE
YOU LOOKING AT?" And I turned around,
which don't do that. [laughter] If you
go to New York City and you hear
somebody behind you yelling, you just
keep walking. If it sounds like your
mom, leave her. Like you just leave her.
Car loose. Okay. It was a crazy guy. He
sprinted up. He got my face. He goes, "I
WAS TALKING to you, man. DON'T WALK AWAY
FROM ME, MAN." I GO, "I don't know who
you are, man." And he punched me in the
head. Like I should have seen it coming.
He was like winding up like it was
cartoon. Like he was like, "Popey, like
Papey." He's like winding up and he hit
me. At that point, I hadn't been hit in
about 20 years. And I forgot what you
were supposed to do. And then I
remembered I used to practice fighting
every day in college and I I wrestled
him. I I did I I I I shot a single leg
takedown to the right side. I picked his
leg way up here like you're supposed to
and he went right down. Like he he
sucked. Like this guy [laughter]
I guarantee he never made it past DR.
Like he just wasn't good. And I and and
I I got on top of him and I lost my
mind. I WAS LIKE I USED TO WRESTLE
MESS UP.
IF SOMEBODY WOULD have walked by, they
would have been like, "There's a crazy
guy [laughter] getting beat up by a
really crazy guy." And it's New York
City, so people did start walking by and
it's New York City, so nobody cared.
They're like, "Oh, looks like Larry's
losing a night." Anyway,
finally, some guy walked by and he
pulled out his cell phone. He started
videotaping us. And that's when it all
came flooding back to me. I'm like, I'm
I'm 46. I'm fighting in a major
metropolitan area on the streets.
There's going to be legal consequences.
And it was the weirdest end to a
wrestling match. I just go, "Hey man, I
got to go." Like I just I just
[laughter]
My mom said I had to be home by 8. Like
I I just I just left and he left and
nobody said anything. Like the only guy
that said anything was a dude with the
cell phone. As I was walking AWAY, HE
GOES, "YO, DOG. WHY'D HE HIT YOU?" I WAS
LIKE, "CUZ HE'S CRAZY. [laughter]
HE GOES, "YOU A CHAMP, DOG. YOU A
CHAMP." AND [laughter] that made me like
proud. I was
I was proud. I was like, "Yeah, at least
one person in this city knows I can
still beat a heroin addict in a
wrestling match if I need to."
[laughter]
And I and I just uh I went home and I
was like shaken up. And uh I called my
friend Mike who had lived in the city
for a long time. And we got to the part
about the cell phone and he goes, "Whoa,
whoa, whoa, dude. This is on tape."
[laughter]
I go, "Yeah, I guess so." He goes,
"Dude, this is going to be the biggest
thing in your career." [laughter] I go,
"Hey, man. I had a Comedy Central
special." He goes, "Yeah, dude, but
people are going to watch this like
pretty close to my son.
My son and I bond. My son and I watched
a lot of football together. That's how
we got close. That's how a lot of men
process emotions. We watch sports
because the sports are up on the screen
safely. That's where the emotions are.
You're sitting on the couch and you can
almost like live vicariously through
what's happening on that screen. Almost
becomes like a metaphor for what's
happening with you. Like I remember
watching a football game this year and
we're on the couch. I'm like, "Wow,
seems like um seems like Russell
Wilson's having a hard time lately,
huh?"
And he's like, "Yeah, yeah, I think
Russell Wilson is having a hard time
lately." [laughter]
I said, "Well, what do you think is
going on with him?" He goes, "Well,
honestly, I I just feel like the coach
is pushing him too hard. He's just on
his back all the time, and he just won't
let Well, that's probably cuz the coach
sees how much potential Russell has, and
he feels like it's his job to help him
reach that full pot. Well, he should
back off.
It's too much.
Well, you know, Russell's a free agent
next year, and then I guess he can
figure out where he's going to get his
own money from,
[laughter]
Dad. Yes, son.
I think Russell Wilson might be gay. All
right, let's watch some hockey. Here we
go. [applause]
I now feel if you want to feel generally
positive about the current state of the
United States of America on a global
cultural scale, what you need to do is
you need to watch 90Day Fiance on TLC.
Cuz
cuz you watch that and you realize
America must be doing something right,
dude. Cuz people all around this world
are lining up doing whatever it takes,
throwing it all the way just for the
chance to make it somewhere in the
Midwest. They don't give a where they
end up, dude. They just want They'll do
anything up to and including marrying
the biggest jabron in the state of Ohio.
Gladly. They'll interview this guy on
there. He's like, "Yeah, my name's
Jason. I'm a 35-year-old dodgeball
coach." And uh ever since my mom kicked
me out, I've been looking for Miss
Wright. You know, like like the type of
woman that knows how to load the
dishwasher and keep her mouth shut
during Buckeyes games. That type of
thing, right?
And you're listening like, "I don't like
your chances, Jason.
you don't seem like much of a catch to
me. Then they cut to some beautiful girl
in Estonia or somewhere like that just
like Jason is man of my dreams.
I often fantasize about being with him
and eating hamburger helper off of
pepper plate.
I'm feeling good and I'm feeling chill
and that's huge for me. That's been my
goal for a while now. I've been trying
to make myself feel more chill, which is
a cooler way of saying I was recently
put on mood stabilizers. [laughter]
Thank you. Thank you so much. I don't
know what they do scientifically. My
psychiatrist says the goal is to turn my
moods into vibes. So, I'm just kind of
vibing out 24/7 doctor's orders.
Mood stabilizers are great. I know they
work cuz like the first or second week I
started taking them, my wife and I, we
went to Joshua Tree in California. I
don't know if anyone here has been to
Joshua Tree, but it's a uh dog town in
the middle of the desert. Our last night
in Joshua Tree, I looked at my wife and
I was like, "Babe, it's our last night
here. I'm going to splurge a little. I'm
going to get takeout from the best
restaurant in Joshua Tree." So, I did a
little research on Yelp, drove into
town, got takeout from this beautiful
little Italian restaurant they have
there called uh Domino's Pizza.
So, I walk into this Domino's, there's
already a man in line. So, I stand
behind him. I sort of nod at him,
indicating I'm chill now.
Take your time.
And this man is just staring at the menu
for so long. In his defense, there are
six things. So, he was overwhelmed by
the menu and eventually he looked at the
young woman behind the counter and he
went, "Um, excuse me, miss. Do you guys
make margarita style?"
And the young woman behind the counter,
she was like, "No, I'm sorry. We don't
serve alcohol here."
And this guy is so condescending. He was
like, "Uh, no, no, no. Margarita style.
That's how we eat pizza on the East
Coast.
And I was like, "Hatred confirmed." You
know, this girl, she's trying her best.
She goes, "Okay, uh, well, can you tell
me what margarita style pizza is cuz
maybe I can make something similar for
you?" And he went, "Oh, I don't know.
I don't know what it is."
And it didn't stop there. They just kept
talking. It was like six or seven more
minutes of these two morons trying to
figure out what he thinks margarita
style pizza might be hypothetically.
And what he ended up ordering was so
insane. He ordered a large Pacific
Supreme pizza with pineapple. Okay,
crazy. Especially when I tell you it
does not come with pineapple. He added
pineapple cuz in his head he was like, I
think that's what makes it margarita
style, you know. But I handled it really
well. I really kept it together. All I
did was every 30 or 40 seconds I would
just take a deep breath and go.
Just the most passive aggressive sigh
you've ever heard in your life.
But for me, that's growth.
Do you know what I'm saying? I hate to
think what would have happened in that
Domino's if I went in there unmedicated.
Like the moment he added pineapple to
his pizza, I would have been like and I
would have walked over to the door and
locked it, [laughter] you know,
and then just held the Domino's hostage.
I would have put a pizza slicer to his
neck,
waited for police to arrive, and then I
make the police negotiator tell this guy
through the window that he just wants a
cheese pizza. That's all he wants. He
wants a cheese pizza with a little basil
on top. He's too stupid to know he wants
a cheese pizza.
So anyway, I'm chill now. It feels
great.
I'm back.
I work in television. Uh I watch a lot
of television. I think I have a pretty
refined taste in television actually. Uh
I mostly watch a channel called A&E,
which stands for arts and entertainment.
It's very classy. My favorite show on
A&E, maybe my favorite show of all time
is a a TV show called Intervention.
Okay, if you haven't seen Intervention,
uh, how do I describe it? Um, well, it's
basically a prank show.
And the way it works is a production
company descends on some awful little
town and they are looking for a huge
drug addict, right? and they find a drug
addict and they go up to him and they're
like hey man um we heard you're pretty
good at taking drugs and he's like uh
pretty good I'm the best you know I'm a
it's all I do and they're like awesome I
mean would you ever consider getting
high on camera and he's like uh it would
be an honor
and then for the first 40 minutes of
every episode intervention they just
follow this guy around as he gets so
high on camera like incredible like
every episode intervention there is a
moment you're like this guy is a pro
like I have never been this high.
In the third act, that's when things get
real, right? The third act, the guy's
comfortable doing drugs on camera. He's
friends with the crew and the main
producer comes up to him and and he's
like, "Hey, so uh I don't know if you're
open to this. It's just a pitch, but
have you ever gotten like super high in
a hotel conference room?"
And the addict's like, "Uh, no, but that
sounds dope. Let's do it. I'm down."
Right? He walks into the hotel
conference room all proud of himself and
then boom, it's all his friends and
family. They hold an intervention for
him. Uh pranked, you know.
It rules.
I think I'm all set on family. I think
I'm I think I'm all good. I'm done.
Family is my least favorite group
project
cuz it's like in school there's always
somebody has to do the majority of the
work, right? And it's never the dad.
[laughter]
It's never the dad. It's not the dad.
Everyone I know was raised by their mom
and executive produced by their dad,
right? You need him to get the project
made, but he isn't like in the editing
bay.
He's just showing up like this is all my
money's getting. NO,
[laughter]
I've been working on my relationship
with my executive producer
and we had a breakthrough recently. He
texted me. My dad texted me and the text
just said, "I trust you're doing well."
And I was like, "Ah, I guess my dad and
I dated. [laughter]
We split up. It wasn't mutual. That
makes sense why we've been like this.
I don't blame my dad, by the way, for us
being a little distant. I was kind of a
weird kid, you know, like my favorite
thing to do in the summer when I was 10
was watch the Prices, right?
Yeah. Great show, right? I mean, but
also I thought it was helping my
relationship with my dad cuz he was
always like, "You don't know the value
of a dollar." I was like, "Oh, yeah.
I bet you don't know the value of this
brand new jet ski, [screaming] huh? Come
on down.
>> [laughter]
>> Excuse me.
How fun. This is so nice. [laughter]
For some amount of time, I haven't
checked my phone. [snorts] And I love
that. Isn't that nice?
I haven't looked at my phone this whole
time. We're just We're on our phones so
much and we're addicted, right? I mean,
I just said phone. And a small part of
all of your brain was like, "Oh, yeah.
My phone. [laughter] I wonder what it's
doing.
Does it miss me, too?" [laughter]
Like, we're on our screen so much. I'm
worried that I'll have a kid and they'll
like make eye contact with someone. I'll
have to apologize. I'll be like, "I'm so
sorry. He's an old soul. [laughter]
He was just diagnosed with attention
span. I don't You know,
[laughter]
I don't like big tech. That's why I
don't like big tech. I don't like them.
I also don't like that they call
themselves big tech, right? It kind of
sounds like they made up their own
nickname.
Like they switch high schools. They want
to seem cool.
Like we're doing roll call for American
Industries and we're like, "Okay, oil
and gas." And they're like, "Hey." Like,
"Okay, great. Technology." They're like,
"Um, it's it's tech. It's actually big
tech.
>> [applause and cheering]
>> It's actually big tech has a girlfriend.
Uh, it's big tech has two girlfriends,
but we don't use labels. It's big tech.
Tech is big and the biggest is tech. So,
tech tech big big big tech tech. Okay,
great. We got it. All right. And before
we get started, is manufacturing here?
And then the class is like, uh, they
moved.
Jew is a fun word, huh? [laughter]
It's a fun, it's a weird word. It's a
last name. Did you know that? I went to
Jewish summer camp with a kid named Ben
Jew. That's a real person. And Joey
Matzah. Those are real people. I sound
like an undercover clansman trying to
just make up stuff. I'm like, "Yeah, I
went to Jew camp with Benj and Joey
Matzah and Drrele Bagelstein."
[laughter]
But here is what I think is weird about
the word Jew. Typically, a slur takes a
proper ethnic term and shortens it. Like
I can't list them, but you know, you
know them all. But Jew is already
compact, right? So people get weird
like, "Am I allowed to say Jew? Is that
okay?" I'm like, "Yeah, Jew. Jew is
fine. Jew is great so long as it's a
noun, right? I'm a Jew. You're a Jew.
It's the adjectives and verbs that'll
get you in trouble." Like, "Yeah, my Jew
lawyer tried to chew me out of five
grand." I'm like, "Whoa, no, no, no. My
Jewish lawyer tried to jip me out of
five grand. See, [laughter] it's better
because it offends a smaller, less
powerful group of people.
[laughter] That's a fun that's a fun
joke to tell because a lot of stuff has
to go right. Right. To even get the
joke, you got to know some stuff. Some
history, some etmology, and then to
laugh, you have to be a bad person. So
[laughter]
that sweet spot, just educated and
amoral. That's That's the fan base I'm
trying to cultivate. [laughter]
Do you guys have those like obnoxiously
named, overpriced doggy daycare places
around here?
>> Those dumb names. Do you guys have any?
>> Yell them out. What's the names of the
places?
>> Dogtopia.
[laughter]
>> I was in Boulder, Colorado. They had one
called Bonjour. And it's like
[laughter]
I bring my dog to a place 50 bucks to
bring her to hang out for the day and
then they text me like they to guilt me
into buying add-ons for her. [laughter]
They send me a picture of her. She's all
sad.
[laughter]
The other dogs are in the back like and
drinking and smoking cigarettes. It's my
dog. [laughter]
[applause] Dog's doing a keg stand.
[laughter]
Hey, text me. For $15, you could get
your dog a compassionate CBD paw rub.
[laughter]
Can you just make sure she doesn't eat?
That's like really all we want.
She doesn't need 12 minutes in the
heated pool with a snuffle pad. Just
[laughter] please keep her out of
traffic. That's all we want.
>> I'm glad we're traveling again. Few
years ago went to Bangkok. Almost didn't
go. Saw a video on YouTube called the
scams of Bangkok.
This dude was a little paranoid. He's
like, "If you go to a museum and you see
someone smiling, total scam.
[laughter]
If you go to a restaurant, they have
noodles on the menu. Your identity's
just been stolen.
If you show up at your hotel, there's a
front desk called Innerpole.
[laughter]
Classic flim flam.
I was racist in grade one. Yeah, I
didn't mean to be racist. I don't know
why I did this.
My best friend was a kid named Ramy
Jakari.
That's how he said his name. I don't
know why I did this. I wasn't trying to
be funny. I wasn't trying to be mean. I
was just six-year-old kid. He was one of
my best friends. But I'd call him over
every recess. Ramy.
Okay, let's try this.
Did I say anything?
Nothing.
Okay, I got some other ideas tomorrow.
I'll see you at recess.
I do that every day. Then I go to his
house for lunch. You ever go to an
Arabic person's house for lunch when
you're six? It's terrifying.
Everything they say, they sound angry.
His father would come in the room.
[laughter]
Okay. Okay.
My dad would like to know if you'd like
peanut butter and jelly sandwich for
lunch. [laughter]
>> I think that horseback riding is quite
overly descriptive for that activity.
Cuz why do we have the word back in
there? [laughter]
Have you all seen a horse before?
Everyone picture a horse right now.
[laughter] Where else are you going to
ride it?
What other option is there? [laughter]
You're grabbing the tail and doing a
little landsk.
I guarantee you anyone who's ever tried
to horse front ride [laughter]
has died.
Cause of death, horse. [laughter]
What do you want to do this weekend? Oh,
let's go horseback riding. Great. How
are we going to get there? H, it's
pretty far away. I guess we'll have to
car inside drive.
[laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> You know, in in England where they know
a thing or two about the English
language, [laughter]
they call it horse riding.
If someone came to you and they said,
"Hey, you know, last weekend I went
horse riding." You wouldn't be like,
"HOW [laughter]
can you be more specific? How are you
arranged on this beast? [laughter] Were
you on top or was it a bellyto belly
missionary type of thing?" Yeah, you
just don't [laughter]
I need a visual.
One night I was sitting around uh my
apartment during the pandemic one night.
I mean [laughter]
more than one, but that particular night
uh I decided to Google weird laws in
Boulder, Colorado.
[laughter] Well, you know, I had some
time. Uh
so, and this is true. These are all
really laws. Uh in Boulder, you cannot
graze your llama on public land in
Boulder. You know, I swear that's true.
And that bummed me out. I'm not going to
lie. I
[laughter]
I had to have a heart-to-heart talk with
my llama. I'm like, [laughter]
I I can't afford to feed you anymore.
You're not allowed to graze on public
land. So you're free to go. Yeah.
[laughter]
Thanks. Yeah. If you ever come across a
llama wandering around Boulder, that's
Bobby. You know, [laughter]
maybe try to point him in the direction
of some private land and let him.
[laughter]
All right. Remember the first couple
months of the lockdown as a just some
real dark days.
Yeah. I just thought I'd bring you back
there.
I remember the first couple of months of
that lockdown. The whole world's caving
in around me. All of us, you know, we
don't know what the hell's going on. You
lost your job. You're in your locked in
your house with your kids.
[laughter]
just washing your mail. And [laughter]
I tell you, man, I found myself doing
all these childhood activities, you
know, like doing puzzles and playing
board games and crying.
[laughter]
Maybe throw in some long showers.
>> [laughter]
>> Sometimes I'd cry in the shower,
[laughter]
just multitasking.
I'll tell you this about the pandemic.
Like, I would rather cry than do a
[\h__\h] puzzle. [laughter]
I'd rather eat a puzzle. [laughter]
thousand pieces. No problem.
And then in the morning I a rustic
farmhouse,
[applause]
[cheering]
[laughter]
which is weird cuz it was a puzzle of a
kitty.
[laughter]
Something ain't right down there.
Something's off. [laughter]
So stupid. All right.
I just don't trust anyone who's never
worked a job where they thought about
killing themselves at least once. Like
at least once. [cheering]
Like once.
You're just like this could all end and
I can end it right now.
I'm not even clinically depressed right
now. But what if
[laughter]
what if I just killed myself? You know
that thing where you're like, "God damn
it, I got 5 hours left in this shift."
Or
[cheering]
[laughter]
swallow 25 aspirin. I don't know.
Whatever it take. When you're
barbacking, all you're doing is washing
glasses and putting them away. Just
stack them, put them away. And there's
two or three bartenders that are slammed
and you're not allowed to make drinks.
And there's beers and ice in front of
you and taps and liquor bottles behind
you. And people are just LIKE, "JUST GET
ME A DRINK. JUST POUR SOME WHISKEY IN A
CUP. IT'S RIGHT THERE. THERE'S A BEER
RIGHT THERE. GOD DAMN IT." YOU'RE LIKE,
"I can't. Please stop yelling at me. I'm
not allowed. I'll be fired. Please, sir.
What are you, a stupid monkey?" YOU'RE
JUST LIKE, "GOD DAMN IT." I remember
looking down at a stirring fork and
being like, "All it would take is just
just two right there." Just right there
and just bleed out in front of this
[\h__\h] looking at him, sit on the
stool and be like, "You did this."
[laughter]
Just break all his drinks in half with
my face and slide down the bar. Clean
this up. Just die right there staring at
him. Still dying.
all behind the bar.
>> You're cleaning this up, sir. You are. I
don't know what you said.
It crosses the mind, you know.
Absolutely. But I think those jobs hone
you and make you into the person you're
supposed to be. If you've never worked a
crap job, you know, that's bad cuz
you're not your your truest self. You
know, think it's like MMA or something,
right? kind of makes you,
you know, tough in your own way and find
the real you. Like I was always a funny
person growing up, you know. I was
always class clown and stuff, but I
would get accidentally hilarious when I
was a bartender, when I was slammed and
I stuff would just come out of me, you
know, that would kill and I'd be like, I
was just being serious. What? That was
funny. Like I remember being so busy in
the weeds as we call it in the industry,
the folks here know. I uh lost my sight.
Like I don't know if it was sweat in my
eyes. I don't know if I was dehydrated,
but my eyesight went blurry. And all I
saw were colors and shapes. That's it.
And I'm just pushing drinks out and
hoping I'm making the right change and
feeling credit cards like Braille to see
who it is. You know, it was awful. And
then some dick somewhere in front of me
goes, "Am I invisible?" And I said
sincerely, "Who said that?" And the
whole bar cracked up
and I'm like, "Yeah, throw him out." And
they did. YOU GUYS LIKE, "HEY, THREW HIM
OUT THE DOOR. I am Caligula."
The only [laughter] way I found out that
we were not as wealthy as I thought was
the first time I went over to a slightly
richer family's house for Thanksgiving
and we all sat on the same kind of
chair. [laughter]
I was blown away. I was like, "You've
got 11 of this one chair type.
[laughter]
Are you SECRETLY A DUKE OF SOME SORT?"
Like every holiday meal at my house
would be like, "IVAN, GO GET THE
COMPUTER CHAIR FOR GRANDMA." [laughter]
I'm dragging it down the hall. I wanted
the computer chair. My mom's yelling out
of the kitchen, "No chance. You are
sharing the piano bench with your
brother.
[applause]
And you know it. We didn't have a piano,
by the way. It's just the bench.
My uncle's at the end of the table
sitting on a yoga ball. [laughter]
Got a hole in it nobody can find. So,
he's slowly sinking for the entire meal.
[laughter]
I was like, I don't think we're as rich
as I thought. [laughter]
So, this was a problem, of course, when
it came to buying a diamond ring. I
didn't know anything about it. I knew I
had to go to a jewelry store. I knew
that I was going to interact with a
commission salesperson at that store,
which I was nervous about because I'm
uncomfortable around commission
salespeople. I'm very easily bamboozled
[laughter]
by their tricks. I'm sure you can all
tell this from my general vibe.
Anybody watching this that works in
sales, as soon as I walked up here
thought to themselves, "This guy buys
extended warranties." [laughter]
I know what I look like. I don't exactly
know the kind of energy I give off on a
first impression. I do know that it
means if I go to any type of ethnic
restaurant, it is a 100%
guarantee that I will be cautioned about
spice. [laughter]
It's not easy getting a medium with this
face. [laughter]
Yeah, I'm a medium. No, you won't. Not
here. You won't.
[laughter] You had our medium. I doubt
it. Guy look like you got a medium
yesterday. We had to call an ambulance.
[laughter]
So, you can have a mild
and a milk.
[laughter]
There's a lot of things I wish I knew
going into this jewelry store. Number
one thing I wish I knew about buying an
engagement ring is you don't get to take
the ring home from the store that day.
Whoops. Wish I knew that. They got to
make it the right size. So, I just drove
to the mall, maxed out my credit card,
and then drove home with nothing.
[laughter] Like, gee, I sure hope they
call.
They did call. I got lucky, I guess. I
go back to pick up the ring. This is
where it gets weird again. I show up. I
was like, "Hi, my name's Ivan. You said
my ring was ready." And the guy goes,
"Oh, yeah. Okay." Then he goes in the
back. He comes out. He's got the ring in
a tiny Ziploc bag like it was evidence
in a murder. [laughter]
He tried to hand it to me like that. I
didn't even accept it. And he goes, "Oh,
do you need a box?" [laughter]
Yeah.
WHO'S PROPOSING WITHOUT THE BOX? THAT'S
THE WHOLE THING. HOW SMOOTH OF A GUY DO
YOU think I am? Then I'm going to kneel
down and just dangle that out there
like, "BABE,
you want to STAY TOGETHER TILL WE'RE
DEAD?"
[laughter]
They wrote my name on here and pen.
Could be your name. [laughter]
So, we were we were at a a we were at a
vegetarian restaurant. Lot lot of
people. I I didn't know all all of them
and I did you know we're there the group
and I made the the mistake of casually
mentioning I was not vegetarian
and this one dude most people are cool
you know one dude what
you'll eat a steak
yeah [laughter]
but you don't want to Watch them murder
the cow.
Nailed it. [laughter]
I love my brother. I don't want to watch
my parents.
[laughter]
You don't have to drag
everything back
to the point
where it's awful. [laughter]
Everything is awful
eventually.
[laughter]
So, I know a couple from back home, back
east. The husband did not get
vaccinated. The wife did get vaccinated.
The husband got COVID, the wife did not
get CO. Do you know why?
>> [laughter]
>> Because the husband was standing in
front of the wife when the wind blew the
co at them. [laughter]
You can be wrong.
It's okay.
When did that become illegal?
You can make a mistake. You don't lose
time off of your life. I was at a yard
sale. Not to brag.
[laughter]
Yeah, I'm a big shot. [laughter] I go to
yard sales. No, we're we're at a yard
sale. And there was this stack of old
People magazines.
People magazines that were old.
[laughter]
Not old people magazine,
not like Matlock watcher, [laughter]
denture enthusiast,
[laughter]
and my favorite, extremely legal.
And there was a a People magazine from
1986,
and the cover story was the most
respected man in America. readers poll.
You know who it was?
>> Bill Cosby.
>> Reagan came in second. [laughter]
>> True.
We made a mistake.
We didn't know.
He was the most respected man in
America.
And then he went to prison [laughter]
and then they let him out.
I think they were afraid he was going to
commit su frazzle frizzles.
[laughter]
I went to high school in the 1980s.
Every guy in my graduating class had a
mullet.
Seemed like a good idea at the time.
You look in my yearbook now, it looks
like I went to high school with a
lesbian separatist militia. [laughter]
One day we'll be like that about vaping.
Seemed like a good idea. [laughter]
The great taste of steam
[laughter]
and the ultimate example of we didn't
know
Michael Jackson.
We didn't know.
and he didn't give us any signs.
[laughter]
Who would have thought that a
glow-in-the-dark skeleton who dressed
like Napoleon and lived by himself in an
abandoned amusement park with other
people's children and a feral chimp
would have such a creepy dark side.
So, I was in the airport the other day
and I [snorts] see this really sweet
sight. I see a woman. She's walking with
her little boy and then the little boy
is walking with this little dog and it
was just like boop boop. It was so
sweet. Um, and the the only thing that
was interesting about it to me was that
the woman was covered in tattoos, just
completely sleeved on both arms, huge
plate across her back. And I understand
that's normal now. That's culture.
I'm just glad it wasn't culture when I
was that little boy.
Just thinking about the tats my mom
would have gotten. [laughter]
Pack of merits in an astrology magazine.
[laughter]
Big gothic font across your chest. CAN I
HAVE FIVE GODDAMN MINUTES TO MYSELF,
PLEASE? [cheering]
[applause] And don't think I'm NOT GOING
TO TELL YOUR father what you did when he
gets home from work. Although, God knows
when that's going to be CUZ IT'S
THURSDAY NIGHT AND HE GOT HIS PAYCHECK.
SO, he's down at the bar with his
friends buying everybody rounds like we
got all the money in the world. And then
he's going to come home and to me they
WERE BROKE. LIKE I HAVEN'T SEEN A $20
BILL SINCE JOHNSON was the president.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Gold. We're all out OF
BACK. WELL, FIND SOMEBODY ELSE. I'M
STILL ANGRY.
[laughter]
NOW, I don't want to be controversial,
but I actually think that sports are a
treacherous place for little girls, you
know, like um I played volleyball
against OJ's daughter growing up.
trail. I'm still alive. [laughter]
No, I did. I PLAYED VOLLEYBALL AGAINST
OJ'S DAUGHTER GROWING UP after he got
out of jail the first time [laughter]
for murder.
It was crazy. He came to like all the
games for two years after. And I'll tell
you what, it was wild being 10 years old
and seeing him on the sidelines because
sometimes after I would score, I would
just look over at him and be like, "Wow,
we're both killers.
[applause]
My entourage,
my grandma and her friends. Yeah,
they're in their 90s. Dude, you don't
feel old around them. Like when I turned
40, I had a panic attack. I was like,
"Oh my god, I can't believe it. I'm 40."
Around them, they're like, "What?
[laughter]
What?
You're just a child.
You're still a child."
And I'm like, "Yeah, I'm still a child."
But I feel bad for them cuz they don't
have that in their life. Like when they
turn 90, they don't have anybody making
them feel better. Like they don't have a
friend that's like 150
to tell them that. You know what I mean?
When they're like, "I can't believe it.
I am 90."
They don't have a 150-year-old friend
like
So, this happened to me. I was driving
by my middle school, and this was a
memory from sixth grade where my sixth
grade teacher, she was our Spanish
teacher, and she would like make the
white kids change their first names to
Hispanic names. What was that?
[laughter]
Does it help you learn? And it's like,
okay, so I'm a Jose now. I don't
understand. I'm going through puberty. I
have enough of an identity crisis as it
is. [laughter] But my best friend Jeff,
he didn't play ball on his name tag. He
wrote Mr. Goodb Bar, [laughter]
like the candy bar.
And here's the memory. My teacher sees
it and she lost her mind. And she goes,
"YOU CAN'T CALL YOURSELF MR. GOODB BAR."
AND HE GOES, "WHY NOT?" AND SHE GOES,
"CUZ MR. GOODBAR IS A PORN STAR."
[laughter]
And I'm like, there's no way I'm
remembering that correctly. [laughter]
So, I looked it up
and it turns out Mr. Goodbar [laughter]
was a very famous porn star in the 80s.
>> But we didn't know that cuz we were 11
years old. [laughter]
[laughter]
SENORITA PRAG
if I may one PRAG
don't say too horny to teach how do you
say that [laughter]
>> last year for spring break we did
Gatlinburgg Tennessee
>> been to Gatlinburg if you never been let
me tell you about it all right
Gatlinburgg is an American Indian word.
It means land of the couples that wear
matching airbrush t-shirts. I don't know
if that's accurate, [laughter] but it's
accurate.
And they always pick the same design,
too. This is what it looks like. It's a
silhouette of a much skinnier couple
than the people who are wearing the
t-shirts. And on the shirt, this couple,
they are holding hands. They're in love,
you guys. Their feet are in the sand.
They're under a palm tree. There's a
rainbow sunset on what is clearly the
ocean in the background. Then they just
write Gatlinburg across the top so that
you know which of the islands in the
Smoky Mountains that they visited,
right? They're just [laughter]
they're not smart people.
But it's great for people watching. If
you like to people watch, this is this
is your spot, okay? I don't know if you
enjoy it or not, but man, there's no
better hobby. It's free. You know, you
just sit there with someone you love and
talk about the trash walking by for a
couple hours, right? Gallenburgg is
prime pickings. I mean, there's not that
much white trash in a dumpster behind a
paper plate factory. Do you know what
I'm saying? Like, it's special.
[laughter]
I love people watching so much. I take
pictures when I do it and trade them
with my friends like they're baseball
cards. [laughter] Now, if you're into
something like that, let me just give
you a tip. Make sure that the flash and
the sound on your phone are turned off,
which I know sounds like a no-brainer.
Guys, I've been doing this a long time.
I messed up bad. I'm in line for
security at the airport. I'm going this
way. Coming at me, he's a gentleman.
Hawaiian shirt, shaved face, but out of
the top of his shirt was this
perm. I don't know the right [laughter]
a tufted.
It was the brightest, whitest, bushiest
chest hair I've ever seen in my life.
And I've been to Sarasota. This was next
level, dude.
It was teased, possibly bleached.
He looked like a Build-a- Bear whose
neck had been slit to send a message to
the other Build-A-Bears to pick it up
cuz numbers are down, right?
[laughter]
And I knew if I didn't get a picture of
him, I wasn't going to be able to sleep
that night.
But here's the rub. I couldn't do it
from this distance and this angle. No
one's gonna see how awesome it is. If I
want some likes, I got to time it so
that when he's passing by, I can get
that side view, you know, the profile.
So, to do that, I have a face I make.
It's very simple. The only the only
thing I'm trying to convey with this
face is what? I'm just checking Twitter,
even though my phone's kind of pointed
in your general direction.
[laughter]
He stops right here. I hit the button.
It's like flash. I was like, [laughter]
there's a Pokemon on your shoulder, sir.
Just
hold on. We'll get it. [laughter]
Just Just be careful. Okay. The other
tip if you're going to take pictures
while you people watch is to make sure
that you have a full battery. Charge up.
because that's what happened to me in
Gatlinburg when I went to go people
watching. I uh I was at my favorite spot
to do it there, which is the
oldfashioned candy kitchen. I love that
place because no matter what time of day
you show up, you're going to see the
same thing. There's going to be a
hillbilly pressed up against the window
who can't figure out how they're making
taffy on the other side of the window
and it's the greatest day of their life.
THEY'RE JUST LIKE, "WHAT? NUH-UH.
HEY, come look. [laughter]
Come look.
It's where they make it.
The taffy for Cracker Barrel. Yes. Right
here.
I don't know how they do it even though
I can see the whole process. This is
[laughter] I saw her standing there a
block away. The Mickey Mantel rookie
card of people watching. I got so
excited. I was like, [laughter]
I've heard about you.
Oh, you are coming home with me. Easy
girl. Easy, girl. I'm not going to hurt
you. [laughter]
Got close enough to take the picture.
Pressed the button. Just a dead BATTERY
SIGN. WHAT? NO. I scared her. She ran
back into R. Please. Believe it or not.
[laughter]
Believe it or not.
And I just sat down on the bench right
there in between the Pancake Pantry and
Fanny Farles Arcade.
I was so mad. You know, all this time I
tracked her. I just let her get away.
>> [laughter]
>> I wish I could pull up a picture so you
could see how awesome she was, but I
can't cuz I was careless. So, [laughter]
I'll just describe her as best I can.
She had early 1990s hair. Remember that
look? Pull back tight in a ponytail but
in the front.
In today's news,
[laughter]
that thing
that thing defied all logic and gravity.
And [laughter] I always wondered how
that was formed, you know, cuz I I I
always only ever saw the finished
product. And then I showed up too early
for homecoming one year and there she
was in front of the big mirror.
Heat.
[laughter]
So that was that lady's hair. Okay.
She's just like she was so perfect.
She looked like someone that might
frequent a Long John Silvers/ Kentucky
Fried Chicken
Twoin one fast food restaurant. You ever
go to one of those places? Another great
spot for people watching. I don't know
what it is, but the average redneck
brain cannot process that there are two
businesses operating behind one counter
and sharing the menu space above. And
the first time they see it, it just
catches them off guard. They're like,
"Okay, could I get a
[laughter]
Okay, what happened here? Am I in a food
court? Like, what?
I want chicken. [laughter]
I can order from both of them. It's the
same company." Oh, I didn't. Okay.
Wow. Okay. Well, I'm getting a family
meal deal. I get two sides. Could I get
a side from this side and then a side
from that side? I can. Okay. Well, extra
biscuits. I knew that before I came in
here. And um
does Long John Silvers have hush
puppies. Ooh, can I do that? Two breads.
I can. Oh, yeah. Let's go there.
[laughter]
And I was wondering like what what is
the big thing here? You know, because I
know that you think I'm joking just for
the sake of doing comedy. I'm not. Okay.
Sit by the sit by the register in one of
these twoin-one fast food spots. 10
minutes tops, you'll hear a sentence
that has never been formed in the
history of words. [laughter]
It's cuz there's too many options and
people aren't prepared and they get up
there and then a line forms behind them
and they get nervous and they're like,
"Oh, um,
do green beans go with tacos? Like, I
don't even know what I'm looking at."
[laughter]
It's the best. It really is the best. If
you're going to do it, and I recommend
you do it, just make sure half of
wherever you go is Long John Silvers,
cuz that is the place that brings them
out. Okay? [laughter]
At any Long John Silvers, you will hear
a grown man ask for extra crumbs, which
I feel is just a new low for our
society.
[laughter]
If you don't know what I'm talking
about, Long John Silvers is a fast food
seafood restaurant. And what they do is
they take chicken and fish and they dip
it in a batter, and then they put it in
the fryer. And when they flip it out of
the fryer, little pieces of that batter
break off. And then a pile of all those
little pieces form. And then people go,
"Hey, man. Could I get a scoop of the
stuff that thing's been laying on? Can
[laughter] you put some of that in my
treasure chest?"
And when I heard it, I was like, "Did
that guy just ask for more crumbs?" She
pushes a button on the register. Boop.
Crumbs. 10 cents. I was like, "You got
to be kidding me. What? How often does
this happen?
>> [laughter]
>> I mean, I thought I could be witnessing
the first time in the history of Long
John Silvers where some guy's like, "I'm
so embarrassed to tell you this, but I'm
a little short on cash. I got a long
drive ahead of me. I'm I'm so hungry.
Could you just, I don't know, put some
of that stuff into a cup? I could snack
on it." No. No. It happens so much. It
has been programmed into the register.
Think about that. If whatever you want
to call that stuff has its own button,
which I'm pretty sure we'll all agree
was not in their original business plan,
[laughter]
that tells me there was a day that
something happened at some Long John
Silver somewhere. Something happened to
bring us to where we are. And as a
people watcher, I'm just sad I wasn't
there to see it [laughter] cuz I
pictured it in my head a thousand times,
right? Some toothless manager just comes
storming out of the back. Hey,
somebody's going to have to start paying
for these crunchies. All right, I can't
be giving this stuff away.
I mean, if everybody's going to ask for
it, we got to figure something out. All
right, I don't know how to make it. It's
an accident. [laughter]
Y'all just love free stuff. That's why
we got rid of the tartar sauce pumps and
switched to packets.
Two per customer. Y'all were just
pumping it right into your boats. Nobody
needs that much tartar sauce. Nobody.
[laughter]
I'm sick of it. He tries to slam that
door, but it's a metal kitchen door
right [laughter]
now. You can just hear him in the back.
I ain't settling down, Ricky. I'm sick
of this. They don't pay me to put up
with it. I'm so mad my hand shaking. I'm
supposed to bowl tonight. Now what?
[laughter]
I'm done. I said it before, but I mean
it this time. I'm done. You watch. As
soon as I can afford that lift kit and
them Luke Bryan tickets, you ain't never
going to see me again. I'm out.
[laughter]
Well, of course I'm going. Florida
Georgia lines opening. I ain't going to
miss that show. [laughter]
They're the only two dudes that even
settle me down right now.
You do that? All right. Well, then you
take the Nelly part. You make me want to
roll my window.
Look, you're kind. You're very kind. All
we just learned is that I've thought way
too much about an incident at a Long
John Silvers that probably never
happened.
And it's really exciting to be able to
tell this joke where people understand
what a garage refrigerator is.
It's wonderful. Okay? Because I live in
Los Angeles right now. And when I talk
about having a garage refrigerator to a
Los Angeles audience, all they hear is
two refrigerators.
[laughter]
Someone must have grown up a
billionaire. [laughter]
And I have to correct him. I'm like,
"Oh, no. You don't understand what a
garage refrigerator means." For most of
the United States,
a garage refrigerator simply means you
finally got a new refrigerator.
[laughter]
And then you said, "Don't throw the
broken one away.
[cheering]
That's for weird." Now, [laughter]
that's for things that should get cold,
but if they don't, that's still okay.
[laughter]
That's for things we don't want around
the everyday milk and eggs, you know?
That's for more loose deer meat in a
ziplock. That's what we're going to put
out in the garage refrigerator.
STUFF FROM YOUR NEIGHBOR THAT GOES in
the garage refriger. You know what I
mean? Your neighbor Jerry shows up. He's
like, "You want to ask ME NOW?" HE SHOT
HIM. LIKE, YOU WRECKED YOUR CAR, JERRY.
YOU HIT THAT MEAT. I know that. That's
hit meat.
I grew up with a thick Wisconsin accent.
But I had no clue I had a Wisconsin
accent until Siri first came out.
Remember that? I was like, "Hey there,
Siri. How in the heck are you?" "Hey,
tell your folks." I says, "Hi, listen.
I'm looking for directions to the
nearest fleet farm. Okay. I think they
got one over there by the quick trip.
And honestly, I got to fill my gas.
Okay? So, why don't you get me
directions to Fleet Farm, then the Quick
Trip, and if there's a Culver's in
between there, I won't be mad. Okay? And
and you know, there are a lot of other
iPhone users out there, and I want you
to know that I know that. So, if you got
to go ahead and get to me last, okay?
Boop. Dialing 911. You are having a
stroke.
Here's a sport I can't watch. Baseball
makes me want to
die.
Nothing happens and it happens slowly
and the players don't care. They finally
put a clock on it, but they need more
clocks on it. [laughter] It's the only
sport where the players don't charge
onto the field. They just take their
time. Everything is taking their time.
They just kind of meander out, shoelaces
untie, they got a big gulp, smoking a
cigarette,
and you're like, "All right, I guess
we're going to start." And they're like,
"Nah, we're going to play catch for
about 5 minutes [laughter]
while you guys wait. Okay, we're going
to throw some grounders, play a little
catch. Matter of fact, we're going to do
it every time we switch sides. Catch
starts again.
So, you watch that and you're like, "All
right, I guess now we're finally going
to start." No, no, no. Now, we're going
to watch a guy in a magic white circle
practice swinging a bat. He's been
swinging it since he was this big, but
he's like, "How's this go again?" Like,
[laughter]
"Like that through."
And then finally he steps up to the
plate and you're like, "All right, now
we're going to go." And after 10
seconds, he's like, "Time out. I just
need a couple more. I don't quite this."
[laughter]
And then he finally digs in and now
we're going to go. No, we're not. Now
the pitcher and the catcher, they got a
little game they like to play where the
pitcher looks at the catcher and he
goes, "Guess which pitch I'm going to
throw." [laughter]
No, that's not it. Guess again. No.
Warmer. warmer. No. No. All these
people. Who gives a [\h__\h] Keep guessing.
Finally, he gets it right. The guy
throws the pitch. Batter doesn't swing.
Whole thing starts all over again.
[\h__\h] Get rid of the catcher. Get a
bucket of balls and just start whipping
balls at the guy. Not next to him. What
is that? Throw it at him. If you can hit
him, he's out. That's the rule.
[laughter]
Now he's going to swing at every pitch
just to defend himself.
And no more resting on each base. Oh,
I'm safe on the bag. No, you're What are
you, seven? Keep running. You keep
running until you're tackled by a guy
from the other team who's carrying the
ball and a bat. Every player should keep
a bat in their hand throughout the game.
I want to see 18 guys jacked up on
steroids, frothing at the mouth,
swinging bats at each other. That I
would watch every night.
[cheering]
[applause]
>> I uh I am I'm falling apart. And I know
what it's from. It's from Little Debbie
Zebra Rolls. [laughter]
I've I've ruined my body by eating
a mass prodduced snack cake. That's the
decision I've made. [laughter]
But they're amazing. They're so good.
And some of you might be thinking, I
love Little Debbie Zebra cakes. Not what
I said. [laughter]
You can shove the cakes up your
figuratively, of course, because they're
hexagons.
[laughter]
can't shove a hexagon up your ass. And
if you can, you're doing Kaggles wrong.
In my opinion, Little Debbie Zebra
cakes, it's not enough cake and it's way
too much frosting. And the frosting is
plasticky, so it gums up on the roof of
your mouth and you have to try to scrape
it off with the back of your tongue.
That makes you look like an idiot cuz
that's how they made animals talk in the
movies. [laughter]
Where's your mom?
WE'LL [laughter] FIND HER.
But what little Debbie has done is she's
taken this cake, which is a great idea
in theory, and she's turned it into a
roll. She's streamlined it to the
perfect ratio of both cake and frosting.
I'm going to tell you something. I don't
know if Little Debbiey's a real person
or not, but if she is, she's a
[laughter]
It's a tough word to say when you're at
half capacity already. [laughter]
>> Cuz I know I'm going to lose people when
I say that word.
And by people, I mean white ladies, and
that's fine. And also men sitting next
to white ladies [laughter] that now have
a don't you dare laugh pinch mark on
their inner thigh. Right. It's like, I'm
sorry. I'm sorry. I know you told me
before we left. [laughter]
Have you ever had Little Debbie Zebra
rolls? [laughter] You haven't? Well,
welcome to tomorrow. You're diabetic.
Yeah, me too. My foot hurts.
[applause]
[cheering]
I would rather hop on one foot for the
rest of my life than give up little
Debbie Z.
They're even PERFECT FOR THE PANDEMIC
cuz you don't have to really grab them
that much. You have to get it to your
mouth and as soon as you do, you can
just flat palm that and shove it in like
a wood chipper. [laughter]
You don't even have to chew it IF YOU
DON'T WANT. IT'S the same shape as your
throat.
YOU CAN JUST SHOVE IT IN. AND IF ONE
GETS STUCK, UNWRAP ANOTHER ONE, KNOCK IT
LOOSE. [laughter]
It's like you're putting batteries in a
flashlight.
It's incredible. [laughter]
>> It is weird that products are designed
now to like make us feel certain ways
morally. And it's funny cuz like no one
knows this, dude. The first company to
do this was Stoers.
They did this years ago. I think I was
the only one who noticed. Stoers had
this thing that said, "Let's fix
dinner." That was their whole campaign.
They didn't do anything. They just put a
fact on all their boxes of food. The
fact was families who eat together more
than five nights a week are 50% less
likely to have children who abuse drugs
and alcohol.
That was it. You would just go, "Yeah,
okay. Sure."
It's got nothing to do with stoers.
Like if your mom's at home microwaving
your dinner five nights a week, there's
a good chance that she does drugs and
alcohol. Dude,
>> I'll take it take it somewhere a little
bit lighter right now. Any any cat
owners in the room? Do we have any cat
owners? Yeah, give it up for cat. Here's
the thing. I I recently became a cat
dad, guys. I am I am a proud cat dad.
And like I never liked cats. My whole
life I never liked cats. I was always a
dog person. Grew up with pet dogs.
Thought I'd always be a dog person, but
a stray cat showed up in my backyard one
day and I was like, "Whatever, fine.
I'll take care of you."
And I love the cat so much. I mean, she
has taught me so much about the world.
But if I was to say the main lesson my
cat has taught me, it's just how good it
is to be hot [laughter]
because she's like a really cute cat.
When I saw her in my backyard, I was
like,
you know what? I'm going to start giving
her free stuff. I'm going to start,
who knows, maybe if I give her enough
free stuff, she might even let me start
touching her. I don't know. [laughter]
Meanwhile, there's all these possums and
raccoons in my backyard. And I'm on the
phone with animal control like, "Hey,
can you guys come kill these ugly
animals in my backyard?"
They're trying to get into the free
stuff I'm giving my cat for doing
literally nothing different other than
being more attractive than them.
[laughter]
I don't want them dead.
So, we had guinea pigs growing up and we
kept them in our garage and in the hot
Ohio summers, they absolutely died in
there.
And my sister reminded me, we named one
of the pigs Brownie, which in retrospect
is extra sad. She was out there straight
baking at 375.
And my mom felt awful. Okay. So, she let
us give him a proper burial in the
backyard. And me and my sisters took
those hard-bodied pigs, [laughter]
not like ripped, but like rigamort is
hard. And
when we buried him in the easiest place
to dig, we put them right in the
sandbox.
And then a couple of neighborhood dogs
came along, [snorts] snarfed them right
up.
It was a tragedy
all around. And I really feel like it
could have been avoided if we just had a
dad.
I don't know what dads do,
but I assume it's regulate the garage
temp.
They're always in there tinkering
around,
planning their escape.
Now, my dad didn't escape as much as he
was asked to leave.
escorted off the premises.
Some of you know this about my my dad.
When I was little, he moved down to
Orlando, Florida to become an actor,
which is not where you go.
He did land a few gigs. Uh he he was an
extra in the television series of Swamp
Thing. Uh he was a truck driver in that
and
that's it. Um
and they took things into his own hands,
started his own business and now he's in
the sign spinning biz. He calls it live
roadside commercials or or character
directionals. He likes to devise a
character and then present it to the
cars. Um,
he's a leprechaun in front of this Irish
pub called the Carryman, for example,
and the rest of his characters are
available on his website.
So, we grew up, you know, around a lot
of costumes like thrifting and going to
Ray Circus of Value and stuff. For
example, like he loves a morph suit. You
know what those are? It's like what
Olympic speed skaters wear, but there's
like no hole cut for your face.
So, you're just like an in single Lycra
suit, just one color, head to toe, no
skin showing. He wears an orange one in
front of the orange Julius.
It doesn't rain that often in Orlando.
And he called me one time after a shift.
He said there was a sudden downpour and
I almost waterboarded myself. I was
like,
I couldn't breathe. It was stuck to my
face. My fingers are covered. The
zipper's on the back of my head. I
nearly died.
I was like, I had to get into the car. I
was so embarrassed.
I was like, it's only embarrassing when
it's wet or
[laughter]
um Yes. My name is Ismo and I am from
Finland. Woohoo. Yay. [cheering] Woohoo.
Uh I I grew up speaking Finnish. It's
very very common in Finland.
And uh I did learn English back then. I
learned English. They teach English
there. But when I moved here, I learned
that it's not the same English that you
have. [laughter] The English here, it's
different. I think the biggest
difference is there's so many of these
things here in America. This um when you
shorten a thing, when you shorten a
thing down to just a few letters, I
think it's called acronym.
Like there's so many of those like FBI,
YMCA,
KFC,
like
so many of those. And I I I've noticed
that people here seem to assume that
every single person knows the meaning of
every single one of these acronyms. Even
people who moved here like 4 hours ago,
[laughter]
from day one I moved here, people just
say to me things like, "Yeah, I'm I'm
going through TSA at JFK.
[laughter]
You want a PBJ?
I have a PhD and I take CBD for my ADD."
[laughter]
And uh
and I'm like, "What the hell are you
saying? What is [laughter]
is this English? I I thought I know this
language
cuz they teach English in school in in
Finland but but they mostly teach words.
Remember those. [laughter]
I know so many words but not these
actually things
cuz even official papers here assume
that you know these things. I move here.
I had to fill out a form. First line on
that form, D O B. [laughter]
No explanation.
Just D O B. Empty space.
Now I know it's date of birth, but back
then I was like, this could be anything.
[laughter]
Dead on the beach.
No.
>> [laughter]
>> Then I did my my first uh first show at
a comedy club in America and the club
said that hey you have to fill out a W9.
[laughter] And I was like what the is
that?
And he said it's a form for the IRS.
[laughter]
Well what is that?
And then he said, "You shouldn't say
that. Don't say that. You should
>> [laughter]
>> um you should you should say WTF."
And and I was like, "What is that?"
[laughter]
Because back home in Finland, we just
don't use these acronyms that much. Like
now, we have a little bit more. But when
I was growing up there, we had two.
We had only two. UFO, HIV.
[laughter]
Only two.
And I don't think we even realized that
they were shortened from something like
we we didn't pronounce them like UFO. We
we we just said UFO. [laughter]
And we still say it like that. We still
It's faster.
>> [laughter]
>> But here it's everywhere and people
assume that. Turns out even in in Canada
I went to Vancouver, Canada. First time
ever. Immediately when I arrived there,
people asked me that, "Hey, have you
ever before done a show in BC?"
[laughter]
And I was like, "You mean more than
2,000 years ago?" [laughter]
Um,
I don't think so. No. Uh, I I was so
young. [laughter]
Where do you find the low-income whites
of this great country of ours? Two
words, Waffle House.
Waffle House seems to be a headquarters
for the low-income whites. Or if you're
in the middle of the country, it's
called a Cracker Barrel.
Cracker barrels are just upscale waffle
houses.
We're in Nashville.
You have waffle houses and Cracker
Barrels. Can you say sweet spot?
What's your mindset when you go to a
Cracker Barrel? I want the unhealthiest
food sold in public,
but I still want to impulse buy a
rocking chair.
Where can I do it? Does such a place
exist? It does. It's called the Cracker
Barrel.
[laughter]
Cracker barrels are closing. Sorry,
whites. Sorry, whites. Cracker barrels
are closing. Sorry, whites. I'm sorry,
whites.
But so are Red Lobsters. Sorry, blacks.
Sorry, blacks. I'm sorry, blacks.
That joke works better if there's more
blacks in the room.
Maybe someday. Right, Nashville?
[laughter]
We don't have waffle houses in the north
where I live. I live in New York City.
We have Starbucks.
And I don't like Starbucks. I don't like
the pretentious energy in Starbucks. You
walk in, everybody's on their laptop, I
guess, writing their screenplay.
You know what I think they're doing? I
think they're laundering money.
something borderline illegal.
So, I walk past the pretentious people
and I wait in line for the bathroom
because I'm in my 50s. And that's what
you do when you're in your 50s. You use
the bathroom every place that you go.
That's less of a joke, more of a medical
fact.
I don't know how it is here, but the
Starbucks in New York, someone's always
in the bathroom for a long time.
[laughter] It's one guy. He's really in
there.
I don't know what he's doing in there,
but he's in there real good. I can tell
you that. He's living his best life. I
don't know if he's finishing college or
starting a podcast, but he's in there.
He's in there real good.
And just when I think he's coming out,
water starts coming from underneath the
door, indicating that he's not coming
out anytime soon.
Last time I was at Starbucks, I was
waiting in line for the bathroom. The
man in front of me had a dog that was
wearing a sweater. I hate it.
It's so condescending.
The dog looked like he went to a better
college than I did.
It looks like he could bite somebody and
he's already dressed for court.
The line's taking too long. I exit the
line and I'm now I'm waiting in the line
for coffee, which is also very long, but
it's moving. And I eventually get to the
front and the girl with the purple hair
goes to take my order and I go, "Medium
black coffee, nothing in it." She goes,
"Don't you mean grande?"
I said, "Miss, I don't think it's the
right time to be teaching me Italian.
There's a man swimming in your
bathroom." [laughter]
None of this is the case at the Waffle
House.
I went to my first Waffle House last
year on the road in Mississippi.
First of all, I love the name Waffle
House. House is in the name. It's very
welcoming.
And it's ironic cuz everyone in the
Waffle House looks like they live in
their car.
I'm talking Waffle House now.
I live in New York City. First Waffle
House, Mississippi. I walk in, I'm
wearing a shirt with sleeves, so I was
overdressed.
I go to the bathroom. There's no code on
the door of the bathroom at the Waffle
House like at Starbucks.
There's no door on the bathroom of the
Waffle House. Come and go as you please.
Little thing called freedom you might
have read about in your history books.
[laughter]
I finish my business and I'm walking
back to my table and it's Mississippi.
I'm looking at the back of people's
heads and it's mullet mullet head
injury. Mullet. Mullet head injury.
Mullet. Mullet head injury. Mullet.
Mullet.
I get back to my table and that waitress
is a talker. OMG.
I knew everything about her in a couple
of minutes.
Mother of five. All cecareian.
[laughter]
I know that because she showed me the
scar as I was eating. Things move
quickly at the Waffle House, guys. One
minute you're discussing menu options,
the next minute you're running your
finger along a cescareian scar of a
woman you just met. Three of the five
kids she had during the lunch rush at
that Waffle House. The other two she had
in a bathtub full of moonshine.
Mississippi baptism.
[laughter]
She's telling me about her life. Turns
out she had just gone through a painful
divorce. She was married to her cousin.
Get off your high horse, Nashville. It's
Mississippi. People marry their cousins.
And I have empathy for that because if
you're dating your cousin, you kind of
have to marry
your cousin cuz how do you break up with
your cousin? What do you even say? Look,
I just want to be family.
>> [laughter]
>> She starts to tear up talking about her
divorce and I'm compassionate. So I
reach up, I touch her face, I wipe away
her tear and I remember I said to her, I
said, "Scalene,"
it was her name, Scalene, named after
the white trash of all the triangles.
I said, "Scayen, you did the right thing
by getting them youngans, youngans as
kids, out of that toxic relationship,
and out of my peripheral," which is a
word they don't understand in
Mississippi.
I see a man choking. He's a big redneck,
no disrespect.
And out of instinct, I yell, "Is there a
doctor here?" Not realizing that I'm at
a Waffle House. Probably not. probably
not a doctor at a Waffle House. Now, I
looked at the people's faces and I
thought to myself, more a chance of a
doctor than a dentist.
No one has teeth in Mississippi. Are you
guys going to get these jokes or no?
So, I think to myself, Michael, you
graduated from high school. You're the
closest thing to a doctor at this Waffle
House. You got to do something.
So, I start to make my move. He's a big
redneck. He's choking. I'm coming from
behind him. I don't want to startle him,
but I know I'm in the south. So, I get
close and I whisper in his ear. I
whisper, "I'm white."
I lock my hands and I start the Heimlick
maneuver, which is gay marriage in
Mississippi. And someone starts
recording it with their phone, I assume,
for Pornhub. Man, after about 15 thrust,
which is what I'm good for,
piece of scrapple shoots out of his
mouth and hits another man in the face,
also named Scrapple. [laughter]
Scrapple Jenkins. He was the sheriff.
[laughter]
So, I head back to my table and I'm
sitting there contemplating the meaning
of life and my waitress, Scalene,
she comes walking towards me and I
notice she's limping and we're friends
at this point. So, I call out to her. I
call out. I say, "Scalene, baby girl,
[laughter]
do you got the scoliosis?"
She said, "Nope. Ferris wheel accident.
Did you guys know Mississippi is 50th in
education but number one in ferris wheel
accidents? It's the silent killer.
There's two types of people in
Mississippi. People who've been injured
in a ferris wheel accident and people
who will be injured in a ferris wheel
accident. It's an epidemic. Any Chinese
people in the crowd? Any Chinese?
>> [laughter]
>> I'm from Australia, man. Oh, you're from
Australia. Okay.
>> Don't worry, they get uncomfortable.
[laughter]
The crowd get uncomfortable because I'm
prepared for the future and they are
not. SO, IT'S
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> ALSO, [laughter]
CAN YOU PLEASE verify that I was
actually speaking Chinese because I know
some people like, "Oh my god, I saw the
most racist thing yesterday. This white
guy was on stage. He was like, "Any
Chinese people?" And then he chung
Chuning this guy at the second time.
[laughter]
But cancel this guy already. Like, oh my
god,
cancel [laughter] him. Seriously,
yeah, it is. It's, you know, it's weird
having a food allergy cuz like, you
know, people on like weird diets all try
to recruit you when they find out.
They're like, like my brother was a
vegan for a while. He's like, "Dude, you
got to go plant-based." He almost had
me. Like, I do like the idea of not
hurting animals. I was like, "That is
pretty compelling." But I have a problem
where I always see both sides of things.
So, I also kind of dig the idea of
killing a creature and absorbing its
powers by eating its flesh. [laughter]
So, now I have to go to Whole Foods. You
know, if you have a food allergy, you
have to go to Whole Foods. They have all
the stuff you need. It's annoying
because it's all so expensive. The food
there is just ridiculous. And it's also
like a culture shock to go from like a
normal Philadelphia grocery store to
Whole Foods.
>> Going to Whole Foods, everyone's all
like they're all peppy like, "Well, hey,
what's up, man?" Like, I'm used to like
regular cashiers like an acme.
Just ladies justing slumped and
defeated, dude.
Just a grandom with two big wrist guards
on their arms and slugging a deer park
like
[laughter]
just wiping tears off the belt.
Like that's what I'm talking about.
[laughter]
You going to Whole Foods, they pick up
every item like, "Oh, what's this? I
never had this before." It's like, "Of
course you have. You're a cashier. You
can't afford this."
The [\h__\h] the bag.
Everything there is expensive, dude.
Everything at Whole Foods is super
expensive. And the reason why it's kind
of a weird reason. Like every product at
Whole Foods is designed to make you feel
like you're a good person. Like
everything you pick up a bag of sugar,
it's like 2% of the proceeds of the
sugar go towards some kid in a up
country.
The kid is so sad.
He's having such a bad life. And his
mom's mean to him, too.
And if you buy the sugar, we'll give him
some shoes, maybe. And you're like, "Oh,
that's nice.
I get all invested. I'm like, "My boy's
out there." [laughter]
You fill your cart with all this stuff.
You're like, "Dude, I am a good guy."
Then you go check out and you see the
sales tax. You're like, "Ah, that goes
towards bombs for that same kid." Dang
it.
>> Shoot. [applause] It does.
But then you I I brightsideed. I'm like,
"Yeah, maybe we'll get the shoes first.
That'd be nice. You know, like
[laughter]
pilot flies away from decimating a
village. Like, you see the moccasins on
that kid? Holy.
[laughter]
It's nice to know there's good people in
the world doing the important work.
I think there should be maybe a soft
holiday around now. At least something
in the calendar that tells people
specifically stop saying happy new year.
[laughter]
I think that goes off for the Thank you
for agreeing.
>> [laughter]
>> I don't know when the date should be.
Some people they they discuss it. I
think I don't know. I don't like it on
January 1st. It could be midnight.
People be like, "Happy New Year." I'm
like, "Chill out. Nothing happened yet."
[laughter]
It's like, "You're about to jinx us. We
about to have a terrible year cuz you
can't shut up." [laughter]
That's kind of selfish.
[snorts] Technically, on paper, we've
had some good ones. Dud. I don't know if
anybody paying attention. Last year was
our Jordan year.
Yeah, just figured that out, right? That
sucks. [laughter]
It's all good. This was a good one. Can
anybody guess what this year is?
>> Kobe. That's right. Can you guess what
next year is?
It's the year Leonardo DiCaprio leaves
us. So,
[laughter]
prepare yourself now. Aren't you glad I
said something? [laughter]
You would have been blindsided in a
year. You don't deserve that.
Now you can look back like, "Oh yeah,
that comedian did say something.
[laughter]
Super funny. Very professional."
Not even that high. [clears throat]
[laughter]
[snorts]
N 20 last year was fine. I guess I
learned a few things. Uh
what's one thing? Oh, I learned that uh
LLBAN is a clothing store.
This whole time I thought it was a
coffee shop.
>> I don't even drink coffee, so I never
walked in to fact check. I just kind of
lived in this lie, just oblivious
in a bubble. I was even arrogant about
it. I even seen people like LLB on their
shirt. I just thought it was merch.
I'm like, they must really love those
coffee grounds.
I was like, I cannot relate.
>> [laughter]
>> was supposed to go to the movies this
past weekend. Got kicked out the group
chat. Uh,
it happens. It's pretty normal
occurrence. Uh,
[laughter]
I told them I was going to bring a neck
pillow and I think that was just too
much for them to wrap their mind around.
[laughter]
They living in the past.
I guess it's fine. You see somebody at
the airport neck pillow, you're like,
"Yeah, this makes sense." But you see me
at the [laughter] at the movie theater
trying to get down your aisle with like
popcorn. What's the thought that comes
your like, "Oh snap, this dude's living
in 2040. How do I become a genius like
that?" [laughter]
Obviously, this guy prioritizes comfort,
which I do. That is right. Uh like I
just want to back scratcher in a trivia
game.
thought it was a pretty mid gift and I
used it. Changed my life. [laughter]
I like scratched my own back. I was
like, "Oh, I don't need a girlfriend. I
could just do this by myself.
Just supporting me." I'm like, "You got
this.
[laughter] I'm overusing the back
scratch. I'm using it in places I can
reach. I'm in the front just scratching
away. [laughter]
Thinking to myself, why are we limiting
this? Why we calling it a back
scratcher? It could just be a scratcher.
That's real oppressive. [laughter]
Let your imagination go. Use it on a
lottery ticket. Do whatever you want.
Reinvent things. [laughter]
[snorts] What else did we learn? Oh, I
learned that uh July 1st is Canada Day
last year.
Same response I had.
That's fine. That was honest.
Don't be upset with yourself.
[laughter]
I read somewhere that the most marked up
bottle of wine on a restaurant's wine
list is the second cheapest. Reason they
do that is got to be on a date too
embarrassed to buy the cheapest wine,
picks the second cheapest, and gets
destroyed.
>> [laughter]
>> Probably the best thing I've ever read
my entire life. It's like, who can we
screw over here at the restaurant? How
about a guy looking for love who's also
on a budget?
That's why I hired you, PJ.
[laughter]
You're an idea, man.
See, this bottle of pino noir cost us
$150. Let's go 600 on this one.
But I love cooking shows and shows about
travel and stuff like that. I was
actually on the Seth Meyer show once
years ago and the other guest was
Anthony Bourdain. I got to meet him real
briefly and I'm glad it was a brief
meeting cuz I don't want to be backstage
trading road stories with Anthony
Bourdain.
[sighs]
His would be like, "Yeah, I remember
once I was in South America, got bitten
by a snake while I was trying to eat its
small intestine."
Oh, yeah. I was once at a Hampton Inn in
Little Rock.
And they ran out of Captain Crunch at
the breakfast buffet.
I get it.
Poor guy must have had annoying fans
when you're traveling food expert.
People running up to you on the street.
Hey Anthony, here's the deal. I'm going
to Malaysia and I love turkey burgers.
[laughter]
[applause and cheering]
Anthony, best rice krispie treat in
Paraguay. Let's hear it. [laughter]
Anthony, I'm going to Dudeldorf and I
love M piñatas.
[laughter]
I need your top five.
I like that show. Chopped. That's a
great show. Four chefs compete for a
$10,000 prize. My favorite part about
that show is none of the chefs have a
realistic grasp of what you can buy for
$10,000.
[laughter]
I was like, "Chef, what do you do if you
win the $10,000?" Well, I've always
wanted to travel around the world for a
year.
[laughter]
Flying first class everywhere.
Oh, you can do that for another $1.3
million. [laughter]
Here's what you're going to do. You can
fly first class to Cleveland.
[laughter]
Take a mega bus to Columbus.
Fly back premium economy from Columbus
with a 5-hour layover in Cleveland.
[laughter]
Then you're out of money.
>> Chef, what are you going to do if you
win $10,000? You have six brothers. I'd
love to buy them each a Rolls-Royce.
Here's what you're going to do. You're
going to buy three decent skateboards.
Then you make a little signup sheet.
Your brothers can take turns.
Chef, what are you going to do to win
the $10,000? I think it'd be great to
buy my mom a house.
That'd be the greatest. Buying your mom
a sweet $10,000 house.
>> [laughter]
>> Here's what you're going to do. You're
going to buy yourself an updated food
processor.
Then the best wooden spoon. Then you can
make your mom some dip and she can enjoy
it in the house she currently lives in.
[laughter]
Not the $10,000 before taxes dream
house.
Also known as a $3,000 house, [laughter]
also known as a used minivan.
[clears throat]
It's fun being a comedian. Work a night,
have all day to have some weird days.
Had a weird day recently. Went to the
podiatrist. Then I adopted a kitten.
That was my to-do list for a Tuesday.
It was great. I was at the podiatrist
office stretched out, looking down at my
little toes. I was like, "A,
I can't imagine anything cuter than
that.
>> [laughter]
>> 40 minutes later. Holy [\h__\h] What was I
thinking?
Finally found something cuter than my
little toes.
Little baby kitty cat.
It's fun being a new cat owner. Get to
buy her stuff. I was on Amazon looking
at cat treats. Found the brand of cat
treat. There's a bunch of reviews next
to it. Saw there was a one-star review.
I was like, oo, [laughter]
I got to read a one-star review of a cat
treat.
This was the entire review. My cat
didn't like this.
>> How's that, guys? At his keyboard. I'm
going to keep this lean and mean.
My cat didn't like this.
I could just see that guy at home. Hey,
Pockets, come here.
Got some new treats for you to try. What
do you think? Oh, you don't like them?
Well, don't worry. Daddy will bankrupt
the company.
What? Just try a different brand. Don't
be so petty. You don't be so polite.
Pockets. I'm going to crush them.
Made the mistake of getting a kitten
instead of an adult cat. That's a
mistake. She's adorable, but my god, I
don't know who's in for. She attacks me
while I'm trying to sleep. It's gotten
so bad, I've actually checked into
hotels. [laughter]
I've checked into the closest hotel in
my apartment three different times to
get some sleep. Probably $5,000 worth of
hotel rooms. It's a great check in
though. You walk in, no bags, bleeding.
So, you here for business, sir? No,
actually a kid attacked me.
Oh, where you coming in from? Look
outside.
See that building 50 ft away? See that
light on the seventh floor? See that
kitten in the window? Yeah. The one
drinking a glass of rosé [laughter]
smoking a cigarette with one of those
long holders.
Oh, she's holding up a sign. Todd Barry
is overrated.
Where does a kitty learn that word?
[laughter]
It's incomprehensible.
Supposed to brush my cat's teeth. That
was sprung on me recently by that. you
got to start brushing her teeth. I was
like, "Okay, I uh I wouldn't have gotten
the cat."
[laughter]
Just saying. Had I known, I wouldn't
have considered it for one second.
But it's too late. I love her. So, I
went on YouTube looking for tutorials
how to brush your cat's teeth.
[laughter]
Thought there might be one or two.
There's thousands of them, all the same.
None of them are helpful.
They're like, "Here's how you brush your
cat's teeth. First start out with the
world's most relaxed cat.
[applause and cheering]
You got that? No, I don't got that.
Shockingly, I do not have that. Place
her carefully on this table specifically
designed to examine animals.
You can get one at your local veterinary
supply store for $6,000.
Now, take the toothbrush and toothpaste
out. Watch what happens. Oh my god, she
took it from my hand. She's taking the
cap off the toothpaste.
She's brushing her own teeth.
Where'd you get a water pick, baby?
She snuck off to Target and bought a
water pick.
Supposed to schedule playtime with a
cat. I don't know how you're supposed to
do that. I don't want to play with my
cat. I'll watch Shark Tank with my cat.
We'll call that playing. Come here,
baby. Sit in my lap. We're going to
play. Scratch. Scratch. Scratch.
Scratch. $500,000 for 2% equity. Yeah,
that's [\h__\h]
[laughter]
Yes, bad valuation, baby. Yeah, they
better have some sales.
The apartment I live in charges me $50 a
month because I have a cat. It's like a
little spiteful pet fee they have.
Remember being in the leasing office,
signing a lease, guys like, "So, it's
just you and the apartment?" "Yeah, just
me and my cat.
Also, it's not just you in the
apartment.
There's also something this big living
there.
>> Yeah. She's the size of my toaster. You
have a toaster?
[applause]
[cheering] You got to come clean with
me, my man.
All right. I have a couple of spoons
also.
Okay. We're going to go 50 to the cat,
30 for the toaster. Eight bucks each for
the spoons.
I can make that joke last 19 hours if I
wanted to.
Think of all the objects I didn't
mention.
[laughter]
They have cat cafes now. Coffee shops
with cats roaming around in them.
They're great. I went to one in New
Orleans. The only thing better going to
a cat cafe going to a cat cafe alone.
You only thing better than going to a
cat cafe alone? Showing up and being the
only customer at the cat cafe.
It was just me and 150 cats.
I was just walking around like I was the
king. Tell me about the gray one.
[laughter]
Seems a bit moody for a domestic
shortorth hair. [laughter]
Why is the tabby not playing with the
raga muffin? They should be friends.
Let's try a coffee. M delicious.
Coffee always tastes best when you're
drinking near seven litter boxes.
[laughter]
[applause and cheering]
That was a lot of cat jokes, huh?
I'm feeling pretty good about myself.
Um, [laughter]
I made it through the summer without
getting poison ivy. And um,
>> I know that's a big deal for me. I don't
know what that plant looks like.
>> [laughter]
>> Like their their hints are not very
good. [laughter]
Leaves of three,
let it be.
Oh, thanks for the poem, but it didn't
work. This thing has the word poison in
it. Is that how we're handling poisons
now? Rhymes. When it comes to nerve gas,
say I pass. It's not [laughter]
I've been out there in the forest and
those leaves bunch up. I can't count
them. I don't know if that's nine leaves
of three or one leaf of 27. So,
[laughter]
what I decided is no more nature. No
more nature. Here's my poem. If it's a
plant, I can't. [laughter]
In any event, stay on the cement. That's
how I'm going to live my life. I'm going
to start treating vegetation like I
treat snakes all bad. But Greg, it's a
garder snake. Well, it looks like a
snake snake. Like I don't know what the
word garter means, but if I see a garter
mountain lion, I'm leaving. [laughter]
Greg, it's harmless. It's not harmless.
It already made me drop my Starbucks. It
has done harm. Harm was done. Venty harm
was done. [laughter]
Thank you. Thanks. Yeah. Thank you.
Yeah. [applause]
I I don't know. Poison ivy. I I'm trying
to learn though. I I learned this. They
use it for medicinal purposes. They use
an extract of poison ivy to treat joint
pain. That sounds like something my dad
would come up like, "Dad, I itch all
over." Yeah, you do. But you're not
thinking about your knee anymore, are
you? [laughter]
There's a snake rhyme, you guys. There's
There's these two snakes. They look the
same. They have the same colors, but
they're arranged differently. And one of
them is venomous. So to tell them apart,
they have this rhyme. Red touches black.
Friend of Jack. Red touches yellow kills
a fellow.
Kills a fellow.
[laughter] Fellows aren't supposed to be
killed. Fellows are in like barber shop
quartets. It's for he's a jolly good
fellow. Not he got murdered by a snake.
[laughter]
Here's a better snake rhyme. No snakes.
[laughter] If you're out there in the
woods and you see a snake, don't stand
still and recite poetry because
[laughter]
somewhere between kills a fellow and
friend of Jack, you're going to get what
snake experts call bit. It's not
[laughter]
Snakes are horrible. They're terrible.
Did you know this? I if you cut a
snake's head off, it can still bite you
for up to 4 hours. That is true. And
it's the same for clowns. Like,
[laughter]
no. Listen, listen. No. If you see a
clown head rolling around, you stay
away. Like, you can't like you don't It
might be a garter clown, but
there's no rhyme. It's not [cheering]
It's not like if his nose is red, you're
dead. IT'S NOT
>> [laughter]
>> I DON'T KNOW POISON IVY. I don't know
trees. That's embarrassing.
Her house is the one with the big maple
in the front yard. You can't miss it. I
can miss it.
[laughter] I'm going to miss it. Here's
the trees I know. CHRISTMAS.
[laughter]
That's it. That's the only one. And that
one's got to have likes on it for me to
get it. I
just just give me your address. That
would be a better system [laughter] for
That's why they have that system. Like,
don't tell me about architecture. That's
not going to help either. It's the
colonial house. Well, it better have a
guy with a triangle hat and a musket
marching back and forth. [laughter]
It's the Stuckco house. Stuckco?
What is Stuckco sounds like? A clown
that can't get out of stuff. YOU'RE
LIKE, "OH, NO.
I DON'T GO IN THERE, STUCKCO. You're
You're too big. You're not going to fit,
Stuckco. [laughter]
You You wear size 76 shoes, Stuckco.
[laughter]
All right, I' I've been up here for a
while. I I better get to it. Um I know
why you guys came. Uh let's talk about
Walgreens. [laughter]
It's an important issue. It's a complex
issue, but there's a lot of sides, you
know, like I mean, on one hand, you got
to give it a there are a lot of
Walgreens. Like there there's several
Walgreens. I mean, you're always close.
I mean, it's very convenient. Also,
they're open late, but I've noticed
after about 9:00, they're just kind of
open. [laughter]
You ever walk into Walgreens like 11:30
and the lights are on and the doors are
unlocked and there's not one human being
visible? It's upsetting. It feels like
something horrible happened right before
I got there. Like what did a cheetah get
loose in here or something? Did CVS
attack him?
Eventually you'll HEAR I'M BACK HERE.
WELL, don't be okay. Be up here. You're
a business. You're supposed to have a up
here guy at all times. That's what sets
you apart from an abandoned warehouse
Walgreens. [laughter]
Also, when you said I'm back here, you
startle me. I'm too old to ever want to
be startled again. Especially in an
empty Walgreens in the middle of the
night. Next time, maybe you could just
jump out behind the Pringles in a hockey
goalie mask. That'll be fun. IF YOU NEED
SOMETHING DONE BACK THERE SO BAD, WHY
DON'T YOU JUST HIRE another guy? Right
now, YOU HAVE EXACTLY ONE MORE EMPLOYEE
than a vending machine. It's not a good
look.
>> [laughter]
>> You're the number 27 company in the
Fortune 500 and you have one guy.
There's a lemonade stand in my
neighborhood. Two girls. THEY HAVE
DOUBLE DOUBLE double the employees as
Walgreens. [laughter]
And listen, like if you're working
anywhere now at Walgreens anywhere,
thank you. I mean, I appreciate you
working. But let's face it, if you're
the late night worker at Walgreens,
you're not
first strength. Like, you're not their
best guy, okay? And you're a little
weird. That's why they put you on
nights. And [laughter] and and they know
that. That's why they shouldn't make you
do stuff back there. They should give
you two simple jobs. Number one, stand
next to the register. Number two, wear
some article of clothing that says the
word Walgreens on it. [laughter]
Cuz when I walk in, I want to know
you're the guy that works at Walgreens,
not the guy that just shot the guy that
works at Walgreens. [laughter]
Another thing, if
if you're a thief, if anybody in here is
like a shoplifter, or you you know, you
steal. I mean, I I can see a couple of
you. I can see [laughter]
I I can see I wasn't going to call you
out soon, but I I mean, if you're a
thief and you go to Walgreens at 11:30
at night and there's not one human being
visible, take a couple of things. Like,
just take some stuff. That's how we're
going to get a permanent up here, guy,
is if you dirt bags start stealing late,
[laughter]
they will staff up. Now, listen to me.
Listen to me. Stealing is wrong. It's
bad. If you don't steal, don't start.
I'm just saying if you happen to steal
from Walgreens during the day,
could you go a little bit later? Like
that. It's just it's going to be better
for you. You're going to get way more
stuff. Honestly, that like it's
trick-or-treating there after 11. Like
nobody's watching. And [laughter] if if
you get in trouble, you're fine. Go in
front of the judge and say, "Your honor,
I walked in. There was not one human
being visible. How was I supposed to
know it was a store?" It felt more like
a place where you just take stuff. You
know that take a penny, leave a penny
thing. It felt like that except for you
take a lot of stuff and you leave it.
You leave. You just you leave. You
leave. [laughter]
They're not They're They're not good at
night. I mean, they're better during the
day. They're They're not killing it, but
they're They're better. [laughter]
They're better. You go during the day,
there's going to be a up here guy, okay?
There's going to be somebody next to the
register, but one somebody. Okay, that
line could get to like seven people.
Still one. It's got to get to like 11.
Then they go, "Chuck, we need you to
come up front. Wait a minute. You had an
extra guy back there the whole time. Now
I'm angry. Okay, Chuck, when you do go
up front, I better see you hustle. Okay,
you better [laughter] sprint to the
front. And when you get up there, you
better act like you're sorry for what
you did to everybody in this line. Just
get right to work. Scan, scan, scan. No
chitchat. Scan, scan, scan. No chitchat.
Matter of fact, if you're a customer at
Walgreens and you get to the front of
the line, no chitchat from you either.
You can talk to the cashier, but
business conversation
only. This goes mostly for you old guys.
Okay? I know.
I know that's the highlight of your day,
sir. I know. I know you've been waiting
to get in THERE ALL MORNING AND CHAT IT
UP WITH THE CASHIER, [laughter] BUT WE
DON'T WANT TO HEAR IT, RIGHT? YOU THINK
WE'RE GOING TO GET ANY RAIN TONIGHT? LY,
shut up. Shut up, old man. [laughter]
SHUT UP. WE'RE NOT TIRED BACK HERE. JUST
GET TO YOUR BUSINESS TALK. WE KNOW YOU
HAVE BUSINESS TALK CUZ THERE'S NEVER
BEEN ONE OLD GUY THAT GOT TO THE FRONT
OF THE LINE AT WALGREENS AND THEN NOT
have some sort of a price DISCREPANCY
EVERY TIME. EVERY TIME. A$1.25 FOR A
SNICKER BAR. The circular said 18 cents.
The circular
THE CIRCULAR FROM 1756 MIGHT HAVE SAID
THAT PRICE, SIR. [laughter]
>> ALSO, when you walk into Walgreens, they
have shopping carts. No, [laughter]
no,
no. I have met your employees and they
cannot handle [laughter]
that kind of volume. Like I I have seen
them struggle with two items. Now, we're
going to encourage people to get 54.
>> [laughter]
>> That's a bad idea. Everybody in this
room knows the unwritten rule at
Walgreens. Whatever you can hold in your
hand, that's how much you can buy. If
you [laughter] if you need more, you
turn around, you go to Target. That's a
Target trip. You don't bring a Target
trip to Walgreens.
And God forbid an old person gets their
hands on one of those carts, they'll
have to shut it down. Sorry guys,
Walgreens is closed. Mort got a cart.
[laughter]
Listen,
you know, I think you guys are looking
at me like, "Well, this guy hates
Walgreens." I don't. I love Walgreens.
That's why I'm so hard on them. I mean,
[laughter]
that's my pharmacy. I've been going to
the same Walgreens my whole life. And
And I think they're good. I I think
they're better than CVS. Close, but I
think they're better than CVS. And you
guys are probably like, "Wait a minute,
Greg. You said Walgreens has one
employee. How could they be better than
CVS?" CVS has one employee for every
five stores. That's how they [laughter]
do it. Where's the checker? He's in
chill coffee right now. Like, he's just
not
just wait. He'll be here. Show some
patience.
[applause]
No. Hey, listen. When I'm talking about
Walgreens, I'm not talking about the
pharmacy. I'm talking about regular
Walgreens. Like I don't think that's the
same company. Like I I bet you the
regular Walgreens workers are not
allowed to talk to the pharmacy people
like don't look at them. They're better
than us. Don't look at them. [laughter]
I bet you every now and then the regular
Walgreens manager tries to go in and
tell the pharmacy people to do something
like, "Hey guys, I was thinking today
maybe shut up, Ted. You got no
jurisdiction here. [laughter]
Go sell pretzels. We're going to HEAL
THE SICK.
>> [laughter]
>> I uh
I mean Walgreens has good stuff. I mean
it. Like they're they're open on
Christmas 24 hours. I I have never
missed one Christmas at Walgreens.
Greg, did you go to midnight mass? No. I
went to 11:30 Walgreens.
[laughter]
Here's what I do. Okay. I have a
tradition. Every Christmas Eve I wrap
gifts and I get sick of it real quick
and I go to Walgreens and I buy a bunch
of those holiday gift bags. You know
what I'm talking way to say, "Hey, I
want to spend money on you, but not time
or effort." Okay, here. [laughter]
Here you want to do it with your gift.
I'm going to throw it in a bag. I'm
going to crinkle up some garbage and put
it on top so we can't see what's in
there for 13 seconds and then we're
[laughter] going to pretend like I
wrapped that gift. That gift is about as
wrapped as bubble gum under a desk. It's
not wrapped. [laughter]
My dad uses holiday gift bags sort of.
When he buys your gift at the store,
they put it in a bag and that's what
you're getting on Christmas [laughter]
morning and it's going to have a couple
of his items in the bottom that he
forgot to take out. YOU'RE LIKE, "OH,
FOOT POWDER, DAD. THANKS." Give me that.
[laughter]
My grandma, my grandma, Nano, Nano was
the greatest gift wrapper in history.
She wrapped our gifts in maps. Is Isn't
that cool? Like, yeah, it was I wish I
would have saved them. My grandma worked
for the defense department in mapping.
[laughter]
She did. She did. And she would bring
these maps home from the office. I don't
know if she was supposed to do that, but
she [laughter]
she did. And And it was great cuz I was
like, "Oh, your grandma has wrapping
paper with Snoopies and Santa Clauses.
That's cute." My grandma trusted me with
strategic bombing locations in May,
[laughter] China.
It is cool. My wife's a black woman. She
can say like whatever she wants. Total
freedom of speech. It's awesome. She'll
like but she'll drag me into
conversations where I have to be like,
"Hey, I don't know if you know this, but
white guys are kind of on house arrest
right now. [laughter]
You go ahead."
Yeah, black women can say whatever they
want. Except for Whoopy Goldberg for
some reason. They're on Whoopi's ass,
man.
It annoys me. She would apologize
recently for using the word gipped.
Yeah, she would apologize to the
American gypsy community. [laughter]
She had to burn 30 seconds of prime time
TV to say sorry to four toothless
carnies. [laughter]
No, man. My wife will just like drag me
into these conversations where I'm like,
I don't know. I don't know how to
respond, man. It's like like I invited
her on a double date not too long ago
and it was like a kind of a weird
situation. It was my friend. He's a
white guy who just started dating this
black chick, which first of all, I'm
kind of like that's my thing.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, that's kind of annoying. And then
and then it's like you don't want to go
on a double interracial date. Single
dates perfect cuz like you guys like
we're saving the world. We're so
tolerant.
Once you're in like a double interracial
date, now you're like enthusiasts or
something. It's
just swirling a glass like we like what
we like, you know? [laughter]
It's it's weird.
But I told my wife the situation. I'm
like, "Come on, man. We should go." You
know, we haven't been doing anything.
Let's Let's go on the date. My wife was
like, "What kind of black is she?"
[laughter]
It's like level two. I don't know, man.
How to can't possibly answer this.
I learn about a lot of white
stereotypes, too. Being with I I like I
hear stuff I'm not supposed to hear.
There's a lot of weirdly specific
stereotypes about white people. You guys
probably have no idea about. I always
like walk in on conversations where I
hear them and I'm kind of like
[laughter]
I I just opened my door. I walked in on
one recently. I opened my door. My wife
was talking to her aunt on speaker
phone. It's a cultural thing. And I I
open my door. I open my door. [laughter]
It's a custom. Be respectful. And I I
just opened the door to her aunt being
like, "You know, white people don't care
about their grandparents." And I was
like, "Ah, damn it, dude."
That one's true. That hurts. That's
I didn't know anyone knew about that.
How the hell they know it's true. My mom
calls me every like 5 months. She's
like, "You know, your great a Bry died."
And I'm like, "Mom, do I You have to
go." I'm like, "Oh, all right."
I I have to go literally ID the body at
the funeral. I go and I'm like, "Oh,
that lady." Uh
I hate funerals. Then you have to like
try to like talk to a dead person in
your head. It's always
>> I just panic. I don't know what to say.
I just like it just like I I just rattle
off some Iced Tea would say on NCIS. I'm
like crime doesn't pay you punk. And I
[laughter]
Yeah. So it's it's fun though, man. It's
cool, you know, being in a relationship
like that. I get like having a black
wife is a confidence booster sometimes.
Certain situations that like dude like
customer service disputes,
bro. [laughter]
Black ladies are like the Navy Seals of
customer service. They
It's crazy. I always I'm first wave. I'm
the scout.
I go up. I'm like, "Hey, uh I noticed
our flight's delayed. Do you know how
long that's going to be by chance?" I'm
like, "Sir, shut the up, dude. Sit the
[\h__\h] down." I'm like, "All right." I
always give him another chance. I'm
like, "Are you sure?"
>> You'll never guess who's following me
up, dude.
[applause]
>> I go, I just tell I'm like, "Uh, it was
that lady right there." [laughter]
She comes back five minutes later with
like a $50 gift card. She's like, "We're
taking off. Throw it on the pile.
Yeah, it's not all fun in games, man. We
do deal with stuff. We still have a race
problem in this country, you know, a lot
of perceptual stuff, you know, like
there's just like sometimes you will
just be looked at differently and I, you
know, it is what it is. Like I I Here's
the thing. I I bought us a pair of
matching sweatpants from Walmart. I
thought it'd be funny. It's not. Nobody
likes it, but they're these like pattern
weird looking sweatpants and like we
still have them. So sometimes like
laundry just works out the way we're
we're just out of stuff and we both wear
them. We don't even think about it.
We'll be out like running errands and
our matching sweatpants and we'll be
like like arguing in the electronics
department at a Target and I'll see the
people looking at us who work there and
I know they're thinking we're one of
those crackhead couples.
I know what they're think. They think
you know those couples that like walk
along the side of the highway together
just visibly bound in failure for all to
see. Just you know those guys they
always make me laugh. I'm like why the
highway? What the hell? [laughter]
Checking Google Maps like I said it's
going to take 5 days and 4 hours. We got
to take the turnpike. Come on.
[laughter]
I love those guys. It's like the heroin
organ trail. You see them out there like
god damn [laughter]
prospectors.
You see their sweatpants catch the wind.
You're like oh my god it's beautiful.
[laughter]
Yeah, we argue. It sucks. I hate arguing
with my wife. I wish we didn't, but we
do. We've been together for so long,
it's like embarrassing at this point,
you know, cuz we we don't even have
anything to argue about. Our arguments
are like they're like abstract. They're
like philosophical battles at this
point. They don't even It's like my
house is like ancient Greece, dude. When
we argue,
like my wife, it's like stupid stuff.
Like I'll be downstairs, she's like,
"Hey, make sure you load the dishwasher
before you go to bed tonight." And my
brain does that thing where it's like,
"Delete.
control altdelete.
I don't do it on purpose. My mind's just
like, "This other thing is more
important." And I just
I hate that I do that. But then the next
morning, you know, it all crashes down
on me. She's like, "Why didn't you load
the dishwasher?" And I'm like, "I
forgot." She's like, "How did you
forget?" I'm like, "You want me to
explain the absence of thoughts?
[laughter]
It's a logical fallacy." And I won't.
We argue over the toilet seat. That's so
embarrassing. I hate that, man. just so
stupid and cliche that you know. But
yeah, she all the time. And dude, I'll
put it down. I don't care. I'll put it
down. Sometimes I forget, you know. And
I'm like, all I'm asking you is justing
gently lower it. Don't slam it like an
[\h__\h] Justing just put it down. It's
not the end of the world. I'm like,
what's the worst thing that could happen
by it being up? She's like, I could fall
in there at night time. Like, what? Do
you run to the bathroom ass first and
jump? What the
>> [laughter]
>> So now I do I put it down every time,
but I also put that little one too. I
put that down like you. I drop that down
and I pee on it a little. [laughter]
You can't win arguments with women, men.
They'll just destroy you. It's their
game. You think you win, they'll wait
like three weeks and just lance you.
It'll be like three weeks later and
she'll be like, "What's up with your
teeth?
>> [laughter]
>> What do you mean? She's like, "Oh, never
mind." I'm like, "What the [\h__\h]
They'll get you with their celebrity
crushes. That hurts, man. Stop. Stop
doing that, man. That hurts us." We were
watching the movie Fury. Did you ever
see Fury?
>> World War II movie. Brad Pitt, Army
Tanks. Awesome movie. We're having a
good time. We're enjoying it. Halfway
through, Brad Pitt pops out of an army
tank. He just like won a battle. He's
like, "Yeah." His shirt's ripped. I'm
like, "Yeah, how does a shirt get ripped
inside of a tank?" But
I'm not ruining it for her. I'm I'm
quiet. He pops out of the tank. You can
see like his stomach. My wife didn't
even say anything. She just went.
[laughter]
Now I'm watching a whole different
movie. [laughter]
I'm rooting for the Nazis now.
[laughter]
I'm googling [\h__\h] I'm like, "Yeah, the
economy was pretty up. No one wants to
talk about it. [laughter]
I wrote a joke a long time ago to try to
shame myself into into getting better
shape. And it it didn't take. I look
exactly the same. I I I I feel I feel
like I look okay from the front. I still
feel good about my front profile look.
Not as happy with the side. And for a
long time, I didn't know what I was like
from the side. And then somebody took a
picture of me when I was not wearing a
shirt or sucking in my gut or aware that
cameras were present. And that was a
real eye opener.
That's when I realized that from the
front I look like a dude who lifts
weights. Uh from the side I look like a
dude who shouldn't cuz it's probably bad
for the baby.
[laughter]
It's a little little rough in the
middle.
Part of the problem is uh I do work out
but I don't work out very hard. I'm not
going to lie to you.
I don't like to go to hardcore gyms. So,
I'm never going to be a CrossFit guy.
I'm more of a YMCA guy. [laughter]
So, I feel good about myself there,
right? I'm a realist. A lot of happiness
in life uh has to do with putting
yourself in favorable matchup
situations. [laughter]
If I go to Gold's Gym or somewhere, I'm
average at best, right? YMCA, you know,
I dominate.
[laughter]
My favorite gym I've ever worked out at
was this old YMCA in Santa Monica,
California. Nothing had been renovated
there for probably 40 years, including
most of the other members.
It was like a nursing home gym.
Those seniors respected my feats of
strength. [laughter]
And they came from a classier generation
that's quick to compliment and I like
all of that very very much.
[laughter] Like a random ego stroke. One
time I was doing the the tricep press
down and this little old lady Connie was
patiently waiting her turn like a decent
person. And uh then when she went to use
the uh the machine, she forgot to move
the pin to a lighter weight and she just
kind of struggled for quite some time.
[laughter]
And then she figured out what happened
and she turned to me and she goes, "My
goodness, you just lived to that."
[laughter]
Well, aren't you strong? [laughter]
I couldn't even move it.
I thought that was adorable.
[laughter]
I also thought, "Of course you couldn't
move it, Connie. Look at yourself.
[laughter]
Like 90 lbs old bird bones
paperier-mâché.
[laughter]
Are you kidding me, Con? I'm pregaming
on creatine whey protein shakes. You
look like you're getting ready on hard
candy and formaldahhide.
[laughter]
Won't you look at that fan, Connie? Look
at it. I turn that fan to high. You're
stuck to that wall. [laughter]
THIS IS MY GYM, CONNIE.
Part of the problem with not being in
great shape is my nutrition program.
It's not great. Uh I live in a house
full of a lot of mixed nutritional
signals.
[laughter]
My wife uh she she says she wants me to
eat better, my wife Lindsay, but I don't
I don't necessarily believe it because
her actions don't go along with her
words. [laughter]
She'll say she wants me to eat
healthier, but then she uh bakes me
delicious treats
cuz she loves me through food. I think
it's competing instincts inside of her.
Part of her does want me to, you know,
eat really well so I can live a long
time and she doesn't have to die alone.
But another part of her wants to fatten
me up just enough so that no other woman
will ever want me. [laughter]
That makes her feel secure and safe.
She'll do this ridiculous thing where
she'll make my favorite treat. like
she'll make me chocolate chip cookies
with like little walnut chunks and then
I'll start to eat them. And she like,
"Dan, what are you doing? [laughter]
How many of those are you going to have
today?" [laughter]
I was going for all of them.
I'm sorry. I thought these were
delicious cookies. I didn't realize you
had baked me shame biscuits and guilt
wafers.
[laughter]
>> Here in New York, we dealt with that uh
what was it? that that terrible air
quality last year for like a couple days
came from Canada.
Brush fires.
I don't know. It was a major
inconvenience. I was like, we should do
something back to Canada, right? Don't
let them get away with this.
I had to search all over my apartment
for a mask looking under old mail inside
my couch cushions. I found one. I was
like
I was like, I hope this is safer.
[laughter]
It was not. I wound up getting CO from
2021. I was just chilling in my mask
waiting for the gift back.
[laughter]
Soon as I put that mask on, they was
like, "There you go." I was like,
I was like, "I can't smell." [laughter]
[snorts]
Not a single Canadian apologize either.
[laughter]
Didn't hear a single sur. That's like
their favorite thing.
You got to pay attention to these guys.
[laughter]
Something new I started this I I got
into uh what started watching more
cooking shows, right? I don't know. It
gave me a different perspective.
[snorts]
[clears throat] You call them Hot
Pockets. I call it Pizza Wellington. Uh
[laughter]
a little bit on the culture side right
now. Thank you.
[laughter]
What else? Got into vision boarding.
I thought you guys would applaud. Uh,
no, it's fine. It's all good. It's all
good. I got into it on my own. I Well, I
saw a homie doing it. I was like, that's
like adult arts and craft. I can I can
participate. Uh, only issue is I don't
know how long it takes to have to like
complete the visions. I keep getting
different responses. Some people say,
"Oh, you have a week." I'm like, "That's
quick." Some people like, "Oh, you have
forever." I'm like, that's way too long.
You're telling me I have until I die to
make it to any beach. All right.
[laughter]
I don't hate that. I want my I want my
vision board completed in a timely
fashion. At this point, it just looks
like a grocery list with cutouts. It's
like Nike socks, deodorant. I even wrote
a note to myself. I was like, "Get a
sandwich named after you at the deli."
Right. That's motivation. That's
probably the hardest thing on there.
[laughter]
Just got a letter the other day from the
uh from the IRS.
Well, I got it like a year ago. I just
recently opened it up. [laughter]
Didn't even get a chance to read it. Had
to throw it right in the garbage.
Was not on the vision board. So,
my hands were tied. Uh [laughter]
I tried to open it. I got like a paper
cut. I was like, "That's the universe."
I [laughter] was like I was like I hear
you buddy.
Lost a uh lost a phone recently. Left
that in the back of a Uber. Tried to
email them to get the phone back. Driver
never replied. I assume he found my
phone. Saw it was an Android and then
threw it out the window.
That's funny. Okay. Um
[laughter] it's all good. I got another
one. So we back. Uh, still requesting
that other charger, right? Nothing
changed. Uh, but I tried to be patient.
I waited for like a week hoping to get
this phone back. Uh, like I said, never
never responded. Uh, which was tough cuz
I forgot how hard it was to have to look
at people in real life.
Like it was just that or staring my
empty hand, which was was a lot of back
and forth.
[laughter]
I was like, I don't want to know my
future.
started wearing headphones, plugged
right into my pocket, just bobbing my
head to silence.
People thought I was rapping to myself.
I was just saying this is BS over and
over under my breath.
Did not appreciate that phone. That's
the problem. I I I took it for granted.
I played a lot of games. Like I would
type in walking directions and then I
would just jump in the car just to
impress my phone. My phone would just
get confused. Be like, "The How'd you
get here so fast?" I be like, "Whoa,
mind your business. You in my pocket. I
pay the bill.
It's not how this works. You got to
establish dominance over your phone."
Let it know that it's not that smart.
All right. [laughter]
I give you life.
It would auto it would just auto correct
words that already exist, right? It just
change them, right? Like I would type in
I would type in the word they uh and
they would just be like thus
[laughter]
confusing all my homies. They would be
like, "Bro, you taking a creative
writing class? What's happening?
[laughter]
Talk to us. Let us in."
Had a homeboy hit me up. He was like,
"Bro, let's go hit this bar, grab some
drinks." I tried to reply back say I was
broke, but it autocorrected to broken,
which ended that conversation.
>> [laughter]
>> I didn't hear back for weeks.
I understood he probably got the message
was like, "I'm broken.
That's too much unpacking." Probably
through the phone.
[laughter] We wound up. We got a We got
a cat. Uh we didn't get a cat. The house
came with a cat. House just We're just
there. There's a cat. Yeah. Was out. We
weren't even sure the cat was real at
first because it was up. Look at it.
Look, [laughter]
it was some real pet cemetery action.
Covered
scrub brush and just missing some ear.
Had like David Bowie eyes, you know.
What are you looking at? Everything?
Nothing. What's going on with you?
[laughter]
Always just appear from around
structures at first. just always wanted
to JUST
[laughter]
It took us about 6 weeks before we
admitted to each other that we saw a
cat. [laughter]
She said at first like, "You see a cat
out in there?" I'm like, "You see it,
TOO?" ALL RIGHT. THANK GOD. [laughter] I
was getting nervous. I thought we had
hobgoblins. I don't know. I'm new TO THE
PACIFIC NORTHWEST. I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
going out there. Everything's [laughter]
Everything's just fog and ferns. I don't
know what's crambling around in right
there.
So, the cat seemed like it was like
friendly. It wasn't like friendly
friendly, but it was like hanging around
us enough. And so, we're like, well,
maybe it belongs to somebody. So, we
should find out before we start messing
with it or feeding it. So, until we
[clears throat] took some pictures of it
and we went door to door to see if it
belonged to anybody. Also, probably a
short-sighted idea on our part.
[clears throat]
You pandemic global social distance.
Hey, here's the new childless out of
state people going door to door like,
"Is this your cat?" And people like,
"Get the away from my family."
[laughter]
Yeah, you're right. Yeah. [laughter]
The old guy, one old guy next door
answered the door, but the chain's still
on the door and he was just like, "Oh,
that cat. Yeah, [laughter] that's
nobody's cat." No.
THAT CAT THERE, THAT CAT BELONGED TO THE
EARTH. [laughter]
That cat come up from the soil when the
sun go down
and just roams amongst the mist just
eating dreams out nightmares. That's
what they got. Man, just say it's not
your cat, old man. All right. I don't I
don't have time for folklore. I got
other neighbors to harass. [laughter]
[laughter]
Now, we found out from another neighbor
that that cat had actually been like a
neighborhood stray cat for about 16
years. That's the how far back they can
remember. There's a stray cat and for 16
years just been living on the streets of
this neighborhood working off of the
Goodwill of place. So, we're like, "This
is our cat. We are taking this cat in."
So, we got the cat to come inside. This
is our [clears throat] cat. We named it.
As as much as you can name a cat, let
alone one that's been doing its own
thing for 16 years. It's mostly just for
reference between us, you know. So, at
first we were calling it first we were
calling it Helen. Uh, we thought it was
blind and deaf. So, we were calling
Helen. [laughter]
You know what? I didn't name it that. My
girlfriend named it that. SO, YOU'RE NOT
MAD AT ME. YOU'RE MAD AT HER.
And yeah, I will throw under the bus.
YEAH.
[applause and cheering]
All's fair, babe.
She's calling it Helen. I I was calling
it dirt nap. That's why he's called a
cat on account that sleep all the time
and was filthy, but also it looked
deceased more often than not. It looked
that cat looked like it had perished
many times. Like, oh, cats sleep weird,
but like draped over a curb under a car
tire just with its eyes open looking at
nothing. I walked up to with a shovel
more than once.
[applause]
It was like, "Well, this is a sad day."
And it just run off. I'M LIKE, "OH, LOOK
AT YOU. [laughter]
LOOK AT YOU. YOU LITTLE crisis actor. I
[laughter] like
you got an agenda. I don't know what it
is. And that that's what I like about
you. You're mysterious. [laughter]
Little crosseyed ghoul.
Yeah. Dirtnap. Little dirty. Little D.
I'm going be calling her little D for
the rest of the story. Also be referring
to as she and her. We thought it was
female cat. turned out as a neutered
male, but we didn't find that out until
later. So, so Jenny Nooch for gender
neutral is the name for some of the
time. [laughter]
And then for special occasions, we call
her Miss America. [laughter]
And by special occasions, just when you
could say something truthful that may
like mean it's more funny when you could
be like, "Man, Miss America on the couch
again." [laughter]
And if you can time that out, right, for
when like a new mom is walking by an
open window, [laughter]
just they're already against us, so
maybe as well just feed him.
What are they doing to that future
beauty queen in there? [laughter]
We got this cat and we we brought it in.
We're like, how we're going to give this
thing the best sunset years we can give
it. You know, we're going to pamper it.
Uh first we took it to the vet, make
sure it's all dialed in. We took it to
the vet and vet right away the vet was
just like, "Oh, it's got a thyroid
issue. It's thyroid. It's got bad
thyroid. It's got to be on a special
diet. Very special. That's a
prescription diet." There's prescription
cat food out there. Why?
Who's trying to get the cat food? That's
not Okay, man. Man, hook me up. Hook me
up with that Hills prescription, man.
[laughter]
like five cats in a trench coat rolling
in like, [laughter]
"Hello, we're here to pick up for Mr.
Meowser."
Trying to MAKE THAT CAT MESS, DOG. COME
ON, MAN. COME ON. [laughter]
It's a prescription.
You can only get it from me. It's $70 a
bag. I'm like, "All right." You know
what, man? Oo, I know it was middle
pandemic and I was all about the doctors
and the scientists, but the
veterinarians I I
just think some of them, they know they
got that giant gray area of your lack of
knowledge that they can abuse about the
animal king. Like you go if YOU GO TO A
doctor and you're like, "My ankle
hurts." And they're like, "Be an ear
infection." You're like, "Well, you're
bad at your job." But
[applause]
but you go to veterinarian with this
this animal that you love but can't
communicate with and you're like, "Oh,
what's wrong with my best friend, my
little guy here?" They could just say
anything like it's the alternator. And
you're just like, "Yeah, I guess."
[laughter]
You know what? That makes sense cuz his
eyes were dimming in the morning. His
eyes are dimming.
That's a 2003 calico with a lot of
miles. [laughter] Those are city miles.
I I thought the timing belt was going to
go first, but Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
That makes sense. What are we running on
those? Huh? 1,500. No. Okay. [laughter]
That That's with labor. All right. Yeah.
Hey, listen. Hey, real quick on the
side. Say we do this in cash. You got
like a similar model out back that
[laughter]
like you can part out or ethical reason.
Sure. No. Say no more. Say no more.
[laughter] NO. NOBODY'S FRANKENSTEIN
HERE. NOBODY'S FRANKENSTEIN.
>> [laughter]
>> SO, you just got to believe him, you
know. So, so I come home with a $70 bag
of [\h__\h] one day. [laughter]
I open the door. I can see out to the
patio. Little D's outside. She's playing
with a bird. Playing. Bird's dead.
Bird's dead. [laughter]
She's just slapping it against the
house. That's
playing's also a real gen generous term
to describe. She is playing the same way
like inmates play handball. It's not for
fun, you know? It's that's just
maintenance in case goes down. That's
all. The only thing missing from little
D at that point was like a cigarette
behind her good ear and a teardrop
tattoo [laughter] just bitching about
not making parole. Like they got ME
DOING THE FULL 12, MAN. OO. If I get out
of here and see that judge, you're going
to see me right back in here. [laughter]
And I could tell it was a fresh it was a
fresh kill cuz she was about 6 feet out
and getting a good return on her.
>> [laughter]
>> So I come in with this food just shaking
it LIKE LITTLE D GOING TO SAVE YOUR
LIFE. LOOK AT THIS. And she looks up cuz
she can hear. It's selective but she can
hear. [laughter]
And she she looks up. She knows it's
food. She like she looks at the food and
then she looks at me and just puts it
together. She's like she's like, "Oh,
you're going to want me to eat that?
Watch this." And then she just ate the
bird [laughter] just
like at me like maintained eye contact
but ate the bird. And I know cats eat
birds but I was not ready. [laughter]
Like I assumed it was going to be messy
but with strategy. That's what I
thought. Like it's a whole bird. I
thought it was going to be like brutal
but you know with technique getting to
the soft part. Like the same way like
we've all had that night where we get
just get a rotisserie chicken just for
yourself. [laughter]
Those nights YOU GET HOME LIKE CLOSE THE
BLINDS AND GOING ELBOWS DEEP ON THIS
[\h__\h] LIKE THOSE.
That's what I thought I would have seen.
WHAT I SAW AND was not prepared for was
the full-on David Blaine street magic
[laughter] disappearing act that she did
on this bird. just
[laughter]
entire thing disappear. One forest gump
feather just floating down
for a fact. Still looking at me like
[laughter]
what did you what did it is it IN MY
POCKET? OH MY GOD.
Is it just GOING TO BE ALIVE OVER HERE?
THAT IS [laughter] WHAT YOU did is
something I got to call this vet back.
Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> I rag him up right then and there like,
"Yeah, hey doc, [gasps] I don't know if
you got a plan B for this whole thyroid
thing, but Lil Deep been out in these
streets just consuming her own enemies
for the better part of a decade and a
half. So if you got some alternatives,
I'm all ears right now." And that's when
the vet on the phone, he's like, "Oh,
Joel, chicken baby food's totally
acceptable for a thyroid issue, too. You
can feed her chicken baby food." "Oh,
chicken baby food. Oh, the that's 50
cents a jar. You could have led with
that, you [\h__\h] quack. So
that's my life now. When I'm not on the
road, I'm just buying racks of chicken
baby food. I'm just buy full just cases
of chicken baby food. And every morning
that I'm at home, I got to wake up and I
got to heat up a little jar of chicken
baby food cuz now that we're an indoor
cat, we got particular about
temperature. So I got to heat up this
little jar of chicken baby food and I
throw up through my nose a little bit
just [laughter]
When we feed this to our HUMAN BABIES,
YOU WOMEN ARE SAVAGES.
[laughter]
I do that and then I go and then I clean
out the litter pan cuz these are the
things you have to do when you let
vermin live in your house. I go and I
just and to get through the litter pan
part, I just squat over it and pretend
that I'm just an optimistic prospector
and this is my lucky day cuz it's the
only way to get through sifting through
that is to sit there and BE LIKE, "OH, I
GOT A GOOD FEELING." THAT'S A BIG ONE.
THAT ONE'S PURE GOLD. ME AND MA DON'T
HAVE TO live on the front. That's a
poop. Okay. ALL RIGHT. OH, LOOK AT THIS
ONE COMING DOWNSTREAM. WOO! BOY, I take
that to the bank. I buy the bank with
that. That That's just a piss fritter.
All right. Well, THIRD TIME'S A CHARM.
I'LL TAKE SILVER AT THIS POINT. Anything
to get me out of the dusty old wet,
that's a poop, too. I think this CREEK
DONE RUN DRY. That's [laughter]
That's just a fun thing to do for me.
[applause] Cuz you got to be creative
with your chores.
[cheering]
You know, mothers are truly incredible.
She's on top of everything before it's
ever problem. She told me this. She's
like, "I got this app. I want to be
ready when her boys start using a
computer." I'm like, "They're 9 months
old and 3 years old. Do we need this?
She's like, we need this. She's like,
this app will let us know any website
they visit, even if they delete
something in their search history. I'm
like, do we need this?
[laughter]
She pushes a button, up pops up a bunch
of adult sites recently visited on her
home computer.
And my wife was mad, [laughter] very
mad.
And I was like, let me talk to them.
[laughter]
These kids are disgusting. [laughter]
I miss sarcasm. I feel like people on
the East Coast are a lot more sarcastic
than they are around here. You guys have
a good sense of humor, but it's not the
same. Um, I get little I look for it in
people. I remember when we were moving
out of our last apartment into our new
apartment. My wife uh goes to the
movers, which are just three giant
Russian guys. She goes, "We need to be
out of this place and into our new place
in 3 hours. Could we do that? What do
you think about that? That's how much
money we have."
And one of the Russian guys goes to the
other Russian guy. He goes, "3 hours?
Maybe if magic happens."
[laughter]
And I was like, "Good. That is good."
I love knowing that that guy has like
maybe like six phrases
in his back pocket to survive in a new
country and one of them is [laughter]
maybe if magic were to happen.
You know, a big thing a lot of people
are looking for is how to get out of
jury duty. Uh I figured out what works
for me. Just be myself.
>> [laughter]
>> Let's just be honest.
Got called in for jury duty years ago
down in Los Angeles and I was uh
frustrated because I had a bunch of tour
dates. I was going to miss them. You
know, the trial would have been long.
So, I sent in a little letter asking to
be dismissed and they didn't care and
they made me come in there. So, I'm
pretty irritated when I get there. I'm
worried about getting stuck on this
long, you know, trial. Uh had nothing to
worry about. Turns out all I had to do
is just, you know, be myself, honestly,
answer their questions. And they wanted
nothing to do with me.
>> [laughter]
>> When I got there, I figured out you can
ask for another form to be dismissed.
And the last question on that form is
super direct. It just says, "Do you
think you would make a fair juror?" And
I was just honest. And I wrote, "No,
[laughter] I'm a comic. I get paid to
make quick judgments and stick to them.
That's probably what I'm going to do in
your court." [laughter]
Which is kind of true. Yeah. I kind of
trust my gut. And I thought that would
get me dismissed. No, it didn't.
[laughter] You know, the uh I get stuck
in a little jury selection pool. Now,
the defense attorney is asking me
questions in front of the defendant,
which is always awkward that he's in the
room. We're just talking about him like
he's not there. [laughter] Uh, and the
judge told us this guy had just served
uh, you know, four years for the
attempted murder. He's just been
released for uh, the attempted murder of
a rival gang member. Now he's being
charged with murdering a different rival
gang member. So, in my head, I'm like,
great, I'm in a room with somebody.
Definitely getting better at murder.
[laughter]
And I thought that cuz when I saw him, I
thought, "Yeah, he did it." [laughter]
For sure. That's a murderer right there.
I thought he was guilty the second I saw
him.
I still do to this day.
And I'll tell you why. He had a lot of
gang tattoos covered about half his
face. [laughter] Face. That's a
commitment
to have gang tattoos. Not just tattoos.
Gang tattoos. Probably half. Half his
face covered in gang tattoos. And look,
I do realize having gang tattoos all
over your face does not make you a
murderer,
unless you're charged with murder,
[laughter]
then it absolutely probably does.
The defense attorney, he read my answer
to that last question about, you know,
making quick judgments, and I wrote that
as a comic, so I think he thought I was
joking. And he goes, "Have you made any
judgments here so far?" And I was not
joking. And I go, "Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> I think he did it.
It was so uncomfortable. I had to point
at him as he stared back at me
[laughter]
with his tattoo murder face, probably
memorizing features.
And he says, "You can't know that.
You've heard literally no evidence."
[laughter]
And I just said, "Look at his face.
Everybody thinks he did it. [laughter]
And when I said that, I heard some
snickering from the other potential
jurors.
I looked over. I carried at least two
little sneaky thumbs up. [laughter]
They wanted to show their support, but
not get in trouble with the judge.
I had a hot crowd, I was killing in the
courtroom. [laughter]
I wanted to put on a good show.
And he says, "If the police or if the
prosecution doesn't provide enough
evidence to prove him guilty beyond a
reasonable doubt, you have to find him
not guilty." That's his words. You have
to. And I just said,
>> "No, I don't. [laughter]
I don't have to.
I make bad decisions all the time.
[laughter]
I can make one here." [laughter]
And he said that would be illegal and I
got nervous
cuz I watch a lot of crime shows, but I
still don't fully understand what
contempt of court means. [laughter]
But I felt like I was treading in that
direction.
Then I thought, well, you've come this
far. Let's write it out. [laughter]
I was like, I don't know, maybe it is
illegal. You're a lawyer. You know the
law better than I do. But I'll tell you
this, just like bad decisions, I do
illegal stuff all the time, and I
usually get away with it. [laughter]
I was texting about how much I didn't
want to be here the whole time I drove
here today, and no one pulled me over,
did they? [laughter] And he just shook
his head, talked to the judge, and two
minutes later, I was walking in my car,
a free man.
>> [applause]
>> THE truth is every frame.
[laughter]
>> I can't tell ages anymore. I really
can't. Like I have friends in their
early 20s and I also have a puppy
[laughter]
and yeah, I can't tell them apart. Uh,
right. All I see are these energetic
beings running around trying to show
strangers their tummies.
>> [laughter]
>> All right. Either way, they're all out
on the couch. So,
>> look, I know it's tough to tell what age
I am. Uh cuz puberty let me down.
[laughter]
I can't wear a backpack
in public. People think I'm running away
from home. [laughter]
I know some of you are like, I don't
know, that hairline's moving up.
>> [laughter]
>> And it's like, well, I make the barber
do that. Um,
make them do it. Go in. They're like,
where do you want your hairline? Where
it naturally is. Here. I'm like, no, no.
I want to be relatable. [laughter]
I try to take care of myself, you know.
I try to take care of my skin, you know,
but I got a sunburn recently, which is
so frustrating, right? I mean, as a
white person, right? Because we hate
accountability.
But for a week I had to be like, "Okay,
this is my fault. Everything else, no
[laughter]
[clears throat]
looks important, you know. I mean,
people love to tell me what I look like
a lot uh because of the mirror
shortage."
[laughter]
And I got a fun one recently actually. I
was just walking around in New York and
a man saw me and he just said, "Not
another Spider-Man,
right?" I had to be like, "No promises."
You know, it's actually kind of hard for
me not to be Spider-Man. [laughter]
The one that I get most of the time
though that people say to me is they'll
be like, "You know what, man? [snorts]
You look like you could be from right
out of the 50s."
[laughter]
Yeah. It's like cuz I'm a person
and there were people in the 50s. Anyone
could be from the 50s. I feel like what
people say is like, "Yeah, but you look
like you would have enjoyed the 50."
Like inadvertently. I feel like people
are saying like, "Your face reminds me
of the patriarchy at its best, right?
[laughter]
Cuz you got that face of white privilege
but before white guilt, so there's no
wrinkle. [laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> Let's [snorts] see. My parents had kids.
Yeah, a couple of us. That's good.
It was just me and my older sister,
right? And I obviously have an older
sister. That's why I dress nice and
believe in myself, [laughter]
right? Like, I didn't have an older
brother, I'd be dead.
You ever heard a younger sibling talk
about how they were treated by their
older brother? It's horrifying.
I'll be talking to my buddy. I'll be
like, "My older sister and I, we used to
play house." My buddy will be like, "My
older brother and I, we used to play. He
left me in the washing machine
[laughter]
for 3 days." It's like they're so
gaslit, they don't even know that that's
wrong. So, I'll be like, "I'm so sorry."
And they're like, "No, you don't get it.
[laughter]
It was a delicate cycle." Um,
and he used fabric softener. So,
actually, I thank him. I thank him for
what he did. Actually, my brother works
in finance now. Can you believe it? It's
like, yeah, [laughter]
I can.
It's annoying to be the younger sibling
in general. It's very annoying because
family is assigned roles on a first
come, first- serve basis.
So, if you're the youngest, you just get
whatever's left, right? Like my sister
got car sick so I couldn't
[laughter]
like I did I just like wasn't allowed.
My parents were like you can't be car
sick but here's what you can be
accommodating.
[laughter]
And I really am you know excuse me the
um [laughter]
no you
[laughter]
there's a lot to accommodate in my
family too. Very anxious group you know.
My first hand-me-down was actually a
Xanax prescription. And [laughter]
yeah, the dosage was a little big, but I
grew into it, you know, no problem.
We all had our own little like flavor of
mental disorder, own little twist. Like
my mom had uh social anxiety, my sister
had general anxiety, and my dad was an
optimist. And [laughter]
yeah, so you've heard of this. I mean,
such a cruel disorder, right? And
there's no known cure, right? Except for
paying attention even a little bit. But
blinders on for my guy. And uh
my particular disorder was OCD. It was
obsessivempulsive disorder.
[snorts] Me too. Okay. So if one
person's going to say me, too. Actually,
we all got to do it
[laughter]
at the same time. So, and we're
recording this, so get it right. Uh
no, my OCD. It wasn't about like uh
[laughter] Okay. So, if somebody's going
to laugh, everybody has to laugh at the
same time.
My idea wasn't about like cleanliness,
organization, which is like pretty
common, but I was like I was just
addicted to these little rituals that I
thought prevented bad things from
happening. So, it's like I wasn't
washing my hands all the time, but I was
like, I'm going to touch his doororknob
eight times.
Now, the dog won't die.
>> [laughter]
>> No, and I know that sounds weird, but I
need you to know that our family dog is
42 years old.
>> A homeowner, actually. They're doing
great. I'm really proud of them. I got
my OCD under control now, which is good.
But my family's always like very
concerned that it's going to come back.
So, like any repeated gesture I do, very
scary. So, my sister will be like, "Hey,
Lucas, I just noticed you're taking
multiple sips of water." [laughter]
But that's totally okay, but I do want
to check. Is that your OCD? cuz I saw
you always look both ways before you
cross the street. And that's okay. But I
did want to check. Is that your OCD?
[laughter]
Cuz I know you told me you always put
your pants on one leg at a time.
And that's totally okay. But I did want
to check. [laughter]
Is that your CD? It's like, no. That's
how people put on pants. So So yeah, I
put them on one leg at a time. It's so
stupid. [laughter]
And I just uh I always go left leg and
then right leg to make sure North Korea
never develops long range nuclear
missile.
But she doesn't need to know that.
[laughter]
I think you could be any witness that
you want to be. I started doing comedy
in Ohio when I first started. Uh my
friends and I, you're always a broke
person as a comedian looking for ways to
make money. Well, my one friend told me
about this thing where you can uh sue
somebody on court television and the the
court show actually pays whoever wins uh
and it doesn't go on anybody's record.
So, we started just making up cases to
sue each other [laughter]
and then just split the money and make
sure the plainif wins. Uh, I was a
witness on Judge Alex. [laughter]
My team won. Uh, and I'm glad we won cuz
I needed the money at the time. Man, I'm
just glad we got this money. I needed
the money so bad. I'm broke. I have like
three frozen [music] hamburgers at home.
Can't afford to buy toothpaste.
[laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> You can be any plainif that you want to
be. I was on Judge Joe Brown [laughter]
as a plainif.
You can be any defendant that you want
to be. I was on Judge Alex again as a
defendant. [laughter]
I went a few years later. I used my
middle name to slip past the producers.
And this one I played a a promoter. Uh I
was supposed to promote my friend's
Battle of the Beards contest. and I kind
of just blew him off and didn't do
anything. Uh, and when I got to court, I
really didn't have much of a defense at
all either. Judge Alex was not impressed
with me.
>> To me, I just things things
communication was failed.
Communication was failed.
>> I agree.
>> What does that even mean? It's
>> I don't know. I just think it was just a
misunderstanding and I I don't
understand why it's got to be like this.
How much weed do you smoke?
>> [laughter]
>> All right.
[laughter]
You could be uh any journalist that you
want to be. U this is a company called
Monae. Uh they're a multi-level
marketing company aka a pyramid scheme.
Uh where the only people who make money
that work for them are the people at the
top of the pyramid, all the executives.
Everyone else just ends up wasting a
bunch of time or losing money actually.
Uh in addition to being one of these
companies, uh they're also been known
for making people lose their hair.
Yeah. They have like skin products that
were making people lose their hair. So I
emailed them uh and pretended to be a
reporter from a newspaper I made up
called the Colorado and Times [laughter]
signed. My name is Jackie Jones. I
emailed them a meme I made of their CEO.
I photoshopped him bald and said, "If
you like the Vin Diesel look, you should
try our hair products because they'll
make you bald."
Uh, they wrote back and said, "It's
absolutely unequivocally not from their
CEO." So, I said, "Okay, uh, we'll make
note that he didn't say anything about
Vin Diesel. However, we do have
something Vin Diesel said about him." I
said, "We can share that with you, too,
before we run our story." They're like,
"Yes, we absolutely want to see that
story and quote before you run it." So,
I was like, "Okay, yes, this is directly
from Vins's reps. I've relied on Monat
to keep me bald for years." [laughter]
So, so after this email, uh the next
email I got was from the lawyers,
uh and they sent me a multi-page demand
letter. Uh, it mentioned Vin Diesel like
six times
and and they said that you can tell it's
not their CEO by a simple Google search.
They said if Jackie or the Colorado
Times publishes this, they'll take swift
legal action. And then they gave me a
deadline to confirm that I won't publish
this. And then said they said if you
have any questions or or want to address
this issue further, please contact us or
have your attorney do so.
So I had my attorney do so.
>> [laughter]
>> I wrote them and said, "On January 28th,
2021, you threatened to take swift legal
action. I'm reaching out to inform you
that if you take any legal action
against Jackie or their Colorado and
Times, even just a tiny hair of legal
action, [laughter] I'll respond by
photoshopping every Monat executive
bald."
These photos will be posted on the
internet, made easily accessible by a
simple Google search.
>> [laughter]
>> In addition, I'll get in touch with
every bald celebrity to ask them if
they'd be interested in promoting Monet.
And that list includes, but is not
limited to Pitbull, Charles Barkley,
Samuel Jackson, Dwayne the Rock Johnson,
Larry David, Seal, Terry Cruz, and the
Dollaly Lama.
You have until Friday, January 29th,
2021 at 8:59 a.m. Mountain Standard Time
to read this email. That time has
already passed. [laughter]
If you have any questions or wish to
address this issue further, please do
not hesitate to contact a Jones.
Sincerely, Jackie Jones. Jones. Jones
and Jones LLC.
Attorneys at Law. You mess with Jones,
you get the Jones.
[laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> So, I shared this online and uh someone
saw it, I guess, and then they sent me a
link to a Zoom party that all of the
executives, all the people at the top of
the pyramid at Monet were having
together. So, I joined as Trey Angel.
Uh, and it got a little awkward in
there.
>> And I see one face I don't recognize.
Who is Mr. Angel? [laughter]
>> Hey, I'm Trey.
>> [laughter]
>> and they removed Trey from the meeting.
[laughter]
So I tried rejoining. I changed my name
really quick and tried to rejoin and it
let me back in. [laughter]
So I was able to say, "You mess with the
Jones,
you get the Jones. [laughter]
You could be anything. But
>> yeah, little but I'm not I'm say I keep
saying get old. I'm not that old though.
But sometimes I wonder like what the
world's going to be like when like
millennials and Gen Z are like the
senior citizens. I just think it's going
to be funny cuz like people we're not
going to change. It's just going to be
hilarious. Just a bunch of 90year-olds
walking around Ivy's like my NFT is lit.
[laughter]
People listening to music LIKE PUT ON
[\h__\h] IT'S GOING TO IT'S GOING TO BE A
new type of old person. It's going to be
funny. You know, this and the world's
going to have to adapt to cater to old
millennials. It's going to be funny. I
mean, in 50 years, you might see
commercials like it's A CANE AND A
SELFIE STICK.
If you call right now, WE'LL GIVE YOU
NINE FREE STICKS.
People still be talking about each
other's social media. Like, you see the
picture Sarah posted wishing Brad a
happy birthday? She doesn't care. It's
his birthday. She's just showing off her
new hip. [laughter]
very transparent. We all know why you
posted that.
Like my least favorite thing about
social media is like that narcissism.
But people just will post anything just
to show themselves off. People love
getting likes. People just love getting
likes. I don't even think people would
do certain things if they couldn't post
about it. Like I think if social media
ceased to exist, I think there would be
a 30% drop in marathon participation.
>> [laughter]
>> I think everyone in their 20s will be
like, "Well, now what's the point in
running? I can't post a photo of myself
at the finish line drinking a craft
beer." [laughter]
To show everyone I'm as fun as I am fit.
I get it though. You like attention for
your accomplishments. It feels good when
like you do something good and like
people know about it. That feels good,
you know? So, I think it actually would
have been kind of annoying to maybe like
do something impressive before
technology and social media because it
would take people a while. It's like f
like if I invented something right now,
I could like repost something and I know
everyone would see it. That would make
me feel good. It feels good. But if it
was like 1930 and [snorts] I was the one
who just invented scotch tape, pretty
big deal.
I bet I would run into people I know
before they caught wind of my
accomplishment. I just be standing there
like they don't know how amazing. I feel
like I would JUST BE STEERING EVERY
conversation towards tape
[laughter]
so I COULD BRING IT UP AND IMPRESS THEM.
I'D BE INSUFFERABLE. I'D BE ON A first
date, she'd be like, "I feel like we're
really bonding." I'd be like, "I know.
It's like some sort of adhesive.
[laughter]
[applause]
What do you want to drink? I'M GOING TO
GET A SCOTCH." I
I just get there early, rip her menu in
half.
She sits down. She's like, "That's
weird." I'm like, "I ACTUALLY HAVE
SOMETHING."
>> [laughter]
>> I MEAN, IF I CLIMBED MOUNT EVEREST
BEFORE social media, I'd want everyone
to know, but I want to brag about it. I
just do find these terrible segways.
People come up to me like, "Hi." I'd be
like, "You want to know what's high?"
[laughter]
People love likes. You can learn stuff
from from likes, though, you know? Like,
I was talking to a girl recently. She
was like, "I wish I knew which guys want
to hook up with me. I wish they would
just tell me." And I was like, "You just
defined an Instagram like." Like, what
are you talking about? If a guy likes
your photo, he doesn't care about the
photo. A guy, he's just reminding you he
would have sex with you. That's all. A
like ON YOUR PHOTO MEANS STILL ALIVE,
STILL WOULD. THAT'S ALL IT MEANS.
[laughter]
GUYS, guys don't care about the photo.
I'm not SITTING THERE LIKE, "OH, PERFECT
FILTER for that bar. Oh god, sick
boomerang."
No,
>> I uh I don't like following women on
Instagram mostly just cuz pictures of
hot women upset me.
[laughter]
Some guys follow these like models on
Instagram and they're always showing
like why they're always showing me like
dude chicken. I'm like no, I'M HAVING A
good day. Why would I want to see
something amazing that I'll never have?
That's torture. If I was allergic to
dairy, I wouldn't follow a cheesecake
account to keep tabs on what I'm missing
out on. You know who doesn't seem as
silly to me as they used to? Doomsday
preppers.
Remember how ridiculous those guys used
to seem? Like, hey, look at that weirdo
with the beard and the bomb shelter. Now
I'm like, wait, so how far below ground
does that need to be?
What is the proper jar size for urine
storage?
[laughter]
It's fine, man. I won't be here. I don't
care.
I'm 45, which means I'm not elderly, but
I am decaying. [laughter] I've crested
physically. Like, it's not getting
better. There's literally nothing
positive in my future from a physical
standpoint. It's not like, man, just you
wait till I turn 50. I'm going to be
ripped. Nope. [laughter]
For the rest of my life, it's this body
or more disgusting. That's what it is.
[laughter]
It's all going one direction. I'm just
talking about pace.
You know when you pull a tomato out of
your fridge, you know, cuz like 2 weeks
ago you were feeling optimistic at the
grocery store. [laughter]
If that resonates with people,
every 6 months or so, I'll be at the
grocery store packing up my usual cart
load of garbage, my diet Mountain Dew,
and my flavor blasted Goldfish crackers
in this weird wave of health optimism
will sweep over me. What if I start
making salad at home?
I'm going to change my life. Today's the
day [laughter] where I transform into a
salad guy. I start throwing produce in
my cart willy-nilly. I never feel so
proud as when I'm pushing a cart full of
vegetables up to the register. You're
right, supermarket lady. That is a lot
of salad I'll be having later.
[laughter]
You losers in line are going to be
waiting for a while cuz she's got to
weigh all this.
No scanning for this kid. [laughter]
You got to punch in some codes for me,
lady.
What is the code for artich chokes? I
don't know. Look it up in your little
spinny wheel. [laughter] That little
paper towel holder with the numbers on
it. Look it up.
Then I go home and I take my $73 worth
of produce and drop it in the bottom
drawer of the fridge and forget about
it. [laughter]
Cut to 15 days later. It's around
midnight and I've had one of those days.
You know those days where you end it by
just staring into the fridge looking for
answers.
[laughter]
You're not even hungry. It's just like
okay fridge, give me something. Give me
something. Let's turn this one around.
Fridge, you can do it for me. [laughter]
What if I get really close and shut the
door behind me? Does that feel like a
hug? Is that kind of like a hug from the
fridge? [laughter] So cold. Just like
mommy.
I spent a lot of nights staring into the
fridge, man. Like, all right, nothing on
this shelf. Nothing on this shelf.
[laughter] Nothing down here.
What the hell is this? Oh my god, that
salad. I totally forgot about salad.
Remember salad? That was that day I was
going to change my life. Oh my god, I
was so high that day. [laughter]
But sometimes you will pull a tomato out
and it's like smaller than when you
bought it. Like it's not rotten, but
it's been in there for a while. So it's
like a little shriveled. When [laughter]
you poke it, it leaves a dent. And you
have to ask yourself, can I eat this
without it making me sick?
Ladies, that is the exact stage that
this body is in.
[laughter]
Oh, you can eat me. [laughter]
But it must be today.
You have to eat me today.
I don't think she's into it.
What about you, Chrome Dome? You want to
get weird tonight? You and me a little a
little sexy. Make this a Valentine's to
remember.
[laughter]
I'm trying to save off the inevitable. I
do go to the uh gymnasium.
I don't like it. I'm not one of those
weirdos who enjoys physical fitness. I
used to go to a personal trainer and I
had to stop because the guy was just too
excited about life. [laughter]
Just bummed me out. He's always telling
me to bring it.
Like I'd be on the bench trying to push
up the bar. He'd be standing above me.
Come on, man. Bring it. Bring it. Like,
dude, I don't even think I have it. So,
let me [laughter] look around and I'll
just bring whatever I find. I was, "How
about you bring it?" And I borrow it for
like an hour. [laughter]
And 10 minutes later, he told me to get
some. Come on, man. Get some. [laughter]
Okay. Why did I need to bring it if
there was some here?
That makes zero sense.
Word play. Uh, [laughter]
I'm making changes. I am making changes.
I'm trying to quit.
Just quit overall. That's my [laughter]
plan for the future.
Quitters get a bad rap. There's a lot of
anti-quitter bias in this country. From
an early age, they tell you, "Hey, stick
with it. Don't be a quitter." The world
needs quitters, people. [laughter]
Without quitters, a stampede would never
end.
Think about it. A herd of buffalo
thundering across the plane just
running. They don't know why they're
running. They're just running cuz
everybody else is running. They'd run
until they drop dead if not for that one
heroic quitter who looked around and
say, "Yeah, not going to do this. I'm
going to go chill by the creek.
[laughter]
I aim to be that buffalo."
I should quit things, man. I stick with
things too long.
But let me offer you some advice that I
wish someone had offered me before I had
children, cuz I didn't know this, which
is this. When you're traveling with your
family, when you have children, and you
travel with said children through the
airport, you can be randomly selected by
TSA, who will suddenly decide to start
peppering your children with questions
to make sure that you are not kidnapping
them. How fun is that? [laughter]
And I didn't know this was even a thing
until it happened to my little family at
Denver International Airport.
We're traveling through the airport,
ready to go. To give you an idea of my
son Malcolm's desire to talk to
strangers that day, let me let me
explain to you his outfit. He was
wearing headphones, not plugged into
anything at all, [laughter]
fingerless gloves,
and winter boots on a 95°ree day.
I ask you, is that the outfit of a
three-year-old who'd like to dialogue
with a stranger? I'd argue not.
[laughter]
And yet, nevertheless, we're passing
through security and suddenly a TSA guy
is in Malcolm's face and he's just like,
"Hey, son. What's your name?" And
Malcolm's like, "Uh uh uh, Malcolm." He
goes, "Okay, good. [laughter] Is that
your brother over there?" He goes,
"Yeah, yeah." He goes, "What's your
brother's name?" He goes, "Ellis." He
goes, "Okay, are those your parents?"
And Malcolm goes, "I think so.
[laughter]
Can you think of a worse answer
than I think so?
No. No is actually a better answer.
No is like it's an uncle. It's a
godparent. Produce some paperwork. Get
to the bottom of it. But I think so.
[laughter] That's what they've been
telling me since they took me from the
campsite 4 days ago.
And when I say otherwise, they hit me so
very hard.
[laughter]
So I think so.
And we were like, Malcolm, tell that
dude where your parent what are you
doing? Tell him we're your parents.
[laughter]
And the guy's like, "Son, I'm going to
ask you one more time, and this is very
important.
Are those two your parents?"
And Malcolm goes, "Uhhuh."
Like clearly under duressh.
And then they just let us through cuz
they're TSA and they're inept.
[laughter]
TSA is like, "Hey, what if we took the
crew of a Times Square McDonald's, put
them in charge of global security?
What's everybody think? Good idea or
not?
We get through the X-ray machine.
Miraculously,
I'm retrieving my bag and this other dad
who was in line, he came up to me and he
goes, "I'm not going to lie to you. That
made me nervous."
[laughter]
I go, "Made you nervous.
If I don't get these two to Reno by
Tuesday, I'm out 150k.
That's my year, bud. That's my year.
[laughter]
>> [laughter]
>> The uh the exception to the rule of of
Malcolm's shyness is is women. He likes
talking to women. In fact, he'll only
talk to women, which I so get.
Men are the worst. If I had the option
of never talking to a man again my
entire life, I would take that option.
[laughter]
But men keep talking to me and it feels
rude not to respond. So I have to
engage. My son, he's under no such
societal constraints. He can talk to
whoever he wants to talk to and he's
decided that's only going to be women.
So the other day, uh, we were at the
park and we were playing Delivery Guys
cuz my son will only play working-class
games. [laughter]
Yeah.
delivery guys, firefighters, EMTs,
construction workers. Something lets me
know he doesn't respect what I do for a
living at all.
[laughter]
So, we're playing delivery guys and a
woman comes running through the park
right where we're playing. She's got
earbuds on. She's jogging. She's minding
her own business. And my son Malcolm
just goes, "Hey, you."
Yeah. like real delivery guy energy, you
know, [laughter] just cat calls her,
"Hey, you."
And she stops and takes her earbuds out.
She's like, "Uh, yeah, yes." He goes,
"We're delivery guys."
[laughter]
She goes, "Oh, yeah." He goes, "Yeah, my
brother, my dad, me, we're delivery
guys."
And she goes, "Well, what are you
delivering?" And he goes, "We're on a
break."
[laughter]
Like, I'm not pretending to know
[clears throat] my son's eventual sexual
preference, but if he ever decides that
it is in fact women, he's already
gaslighting at a high school level.
[laughter]
Once he figures out that women love it
when you tell him to smile more, he's
going to crush.
And I can feel a lot of women in the
room not liking where that joke went.
[laughter]
But I set up the joke by saying men are
the worst. And then I ended the joke by
giving an example of men being the
worst. So I asked you, is it the joke
that you don't like or do you just hate
foreshadowing? [laughter]
[applause]
>> My first job uh I was a teacher. That's
what I did. And uh first job I lied to
get a job because there were no fizzed
jobs. And that completely backfired.
They made me teach grade 12 history.
I know. I didn't even take grade 12
history when I was in high school. So
I'm teaching it and I'm like the 10th
smartest person in the class.
That's not good. Awful. No idea what I
was doing. Had never taken history in my
life. I had to go home every night, read
the chapters myself first to learn
everything, then I'd come in and teach
it. That's how the whole year was. I'd
even I'd even assign the homework like
this every night. All right? Tonight for
homework, like you to read chapters
1 to three, okay? And then stop reading.
All right?
Don't go reading ahead.
coming in asking questions tomorrow on
stuff I haven't learned yet. That's a no
no. We don't do that
cuz that's what the smart kids would do.
Every day I had this kid Duncan. Every
day he had a new question. Sir,
what happened to the Mayan civilization?
What chapter is that? Duncan
15.
What are you a loser? You read the whole
book already.
I couldn't call him a loser. I could
think it.
But that's the thing, right? Teachers
don't know the answer. We don't admit
it. I never said I don't know. I'd lie.
Throw it back on the kids. That was my
trick. Oh, is that right, Duncan?
So, you think I'm just going to spoon
feed you the answers all year, do you?
No, that's not how I teach kids. So,
thanks to Duncan, I would like the rest
of you to go home tonight and look up.
What happened to whatever he's mumbling
about at the back?
[cheering and applause]
[applause] That was my
That was my WHOLE YEAR. IT'S HORRIBLE.
I'D HAVE DUNCAN COME UP AND WRITE THE
QUESTION ON THE BOARD IN BIG letters
cuz I needed to see how he spelled Mayan
SO I COULD GOOGLE IT LATER MYSELF.
THANK God for Google when you can't
spell something. AT THE TOP IT SAYS,
"DID YOU MEAN THIS WORD, IDIOT?"
Thank you, Google Master.
It's horrible. Then you had to come in
the next day, take up the homework.
I still don't know what happened to the
Mayan civilization. Kids have their kids
have their hand up. I'm like, "Put your
hand down, Dave. You got a 30 average.
I'm not gambling on your answer.
Can't ask a kid with a 30 average. I
don't know if he's right or wrong. He's
going to give an answer. I'm just going
to be like this.
>> [laughter]
>> That's a good, good, good. Let's see
what someone smarter than you thinks.
That's how I had to Lorraine,
can you tell us what happened to the
Mayan civilization
and then whatever she would say, I would
vote. How many people agree with that
answer?
There you go, Duncan. It's exactly what
happened right there.
There's a whole year of that. One kid
smoked pot every day. Unbelievable.
Pot. This kid would smoke it every
morning. 9:00, first period. Walk in
stoned every day. Like, I'm stupid. I
can't tell you're stoned. It's 12th
grade. You stick out like a sore thumb.
Teachers aren't idiots. Then I thought
about it. I think the only grade that
kids could have smoked up before class
and walked in without getting caught was
kindergarten. That's the only grade.
Think about it. You could have smoked up
all you want before kindergarten.
[laughter]
Stormed into class.
No one would know. It took everybody an
hour and a half to get their coat and
boots off.
You smoke up all you want.
You'd be taking forever to get your
boots off.
So would everybody else. You'd be like,
"God, everybody's smoked up today. Look
at this.
Who's the dealer?"
Imagine being stoned at the age of four.
That would be hilarious.
Trying to get that piece of crap $8
snowsuit off. Remember this thing from
Kmart?
Had one zipper,
stuttered at your forehead.
couldn't breathe for the first three
minutes of the day. Got stuck 15 times.
You're stoned out of your mind walking
around going, "God, it's hot. It's hot.
It's June. Why am I wearing a snowsuit?
This pot is screwing up my ability to
recognize the seasons.
What kind of crap zipper was that?" One
zipper
went only the left leg came out.
Remember it started up here,
wrapped around a couple times in case it
wasn't on tight enough where we wrap it
up. And then only the left leg. That's
it was made. People making it were like,
"Let the little ptheads figure it out.
This is we don't need two zippers."
So you're stoned out of your mind and
you can't get it off. You're like, "I
can't get the right leg out." And you're
dragging around your snowsuit. You think
it's a dead body cuz of the pot. You're
like, "Whoa, there's a dead body."
[laughter]
You're getting tired. That's a great
grade to be still. Miss, I'm tired.
When's our nap? Oh,
did I miss snack time? I'm starving.
I'm so hungry.
I'm very happy to be living with Chad. I
lived alone for a few years after the
divorce. I feel like if you live alone
for too long, you start to become feral.
Make some noise if you live alone RIGHT
NOW.
>> All right, so that's 12 people who
[laughter]
showered for the first time tonight.
Good for you. I am honored to be the
reason you would bathe and leave your
home [laughter]
because you don't have to do anything
when you live alone. There's nobody
around to judge you and you start to act
like you were raised by wolves, right? I
watched myself do something so unhinged
at one point. I don't know if you guys
have it in your shower where if the
water's been hitting the shower curtain
for a long time, it starts to get kind
of discolored at the bottom. I tried
cleaning it. It wouldn't come off. And
instead of just going and buying a new
shower curtain like a normal person, I
just sat in my bathtub with scissors and
I just cut the bottom. [laughter]
I just went full method. I was just like
>> [laughter]
>> Arts and crafts. Arts and crafts.
I literally gave my shower bangs.
[laughter]
It's not a mentally stable place to be
in. [laughter]
And then of course it really looked
like. So I went to Target and they had
just released fall candles. And I
learned that day that if you smell
candles for 30 minutes straight, you
will accidentally get a little high.
Nothing crazy, but I'm a lightweight and
nobody in the DARE program talked to me
about candles.
[laughter]
So, I was unprepared for what happened
to my body. So, I was floating around
Target. I grabbed the shower curtain I
wanted. And when I went home and hung it
up, it only stretched like half the
length of my shower. And it was so long.
Five extra feet of fabric coming off the
bottom of this thing.
>> [laughter]
>> And my steps sister came over the next
day and she used my bathroom and she
came out and she goes, "Why do you have
a window curtain in there?" [laughter]
[laughter]
I was like, "What now?"
She goes, "That's a window curtain.
[laughter] You didn't think it was weird
that when you hung it up, there was an
entire Met Gala ball gown coming off of
it. [laughter]
I was like, I accidentally got up on
pumpkin spice and I blacked out, but I
don't want to talk about it,
but it's fine. I can fix this. And I
grab my scissors and I just cut them
off.
[applause]
[laughter]
>> I think white people are the only race
of people that like to be scared for
fun.
Like you feel me? Not an attack doesn't
make you bad. Makes you interested.
But not bad. BUT BUNGEE JUMPING,
SKYDIVING, SWIMMING WITH SHARKS. THESE
ARE torture tactics.
Some of you pay for them. [laughter]
That's a curveball.
I just think white people get to have a
different relationship with fear.
Doesn't make anyone bad. I just think
it's an interesting observation. White
people can have a different relationship
with fear. Like I think white people are
the only people you could walk up to and
just be like, "Hey, you want to do
something scary today?" And y'all will
just outright say no.
You feel me? You'll be like, "Well, what
do you got in mind?"
You feel me? BUT LIKE YOU GO TO ANYBODY
OF ANOTHER RACE, THEY'RE LIKE, "NO."
BUT LIKE WHITE PEOPLE HAVE FOLLOW-UP
QUESTIONS SOMETIMES. They're like,
"Well, what are you thinking?" Okay.
Look at roller coasters, right? Theme
park owners know white people love being
scared so much you'll pay for a picture
of your own face terrified.
That's [laughter] their business model.
That's how reliable it is. They were
like, "Yeah, that's where we're going to
get the rest of the money."
I've been in so many white homes and
seen a framed picture
[applause]
of the entire family terrified.
WHY? WHY IS THAT EVEN A THING? I haven't
BEEN IN ONE BLACK FAMILY'S HOME AND SEEN
A PICTURE OF FOUR BLACK PEOPLE
ABSOLUTELY TERRIFIED. And they're like,
"Yeah, that's the time I got stuck up at
gunpoint right there. That's us. This is
where I tried to sell my kids for my own
life."
So wild to me, man. And understand what
I'm saying cuz I understand I'm
generally speaking, right? I'm speaking
in generalities. I understand there are
special case scenarios for everything.
So please like I'm not being
irresponsible with this. Just be on the
same page with me. I'm just saying
generally speaking though that kind of
holds true.
I'm generally speaking
[snorts]
I feel like white people feel fear so
rarely
that y'all schedule it as a vacation
activity.
Like you feel what I'm saying? Like
literally put it on a schedule. You're
like, "At 12:00, we're going to have
lunch. At 1:00, we're going to pet a
tiger." You're like, "What the are you
talking about? A tiger? Huh?" You know
what? No one black has ever said to me,
"I want to go on a safari."
Not once. I got so many black friends,
no one's ever wanted to go. It's our
country. And we're like, nah.
[laughter]
But I have so many white friends that
want to go. Doesn't make them bad. I'm
just saying it's an interesting
difference that you can spot and go,
"Oh, okay. Why doesn't the safari sound
insane to everybody?"
I didn't realize it was something we
were so like polarized on. I thought we
were all of the same mind. Like,
that'sing crazy. And apparently we don't
agree.
I never understood like why it isn't
crazy. You want to go to the zoo without
the walls?
That's what we want to do. You want to
take away my favorite part of the zoo?
THE PART WHERE they can't get me. THAT
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE TAKING AWAY. OH, all
right. [laughter] Every time I GO TO THE
ZOO, I'M PEOPLE ARE LOOKING AT THE
ANIMALS. I'M LOOKING AT THE STRUCTURES.
I'm like, that's a good wall.
Like that net. Love that glass.
I'VE NEVER UNDERSTOOD IT. WHY DOESN'T A
SAFARI SOUND DANGEROUS TO EVERYBODY?
IT'S NOT EVEN A SAFE WEB BROWSER.
[laughter]
You feel me? You ever open up Safari in
front of somebody with Firefox? What the
are you doing, man?
>> My wife Lindsay's a she's a good
stepmom. She's great with the kids. She
gets along with my ex-wife, which is
nice. I get along with my ex-wife, too,
you know, for the most part. Uh, you
know, we try and run parenting decisions
by the other person. She's only done
something once that really really made
me mad cuz she never ran it by me and I
thought it was kind of an important
decision. Uh, just without consulting
me, she just went out and got my kids, a
giant stepdad,
and I didn't care for it. Had I been
consulted, I would have preferred a tiny
stepped up.
[laughter]
It did irritate me for for whatever
reason. I just I I hoped and I assumed I
would be like the bigger dude. And I
just wanted that to be reality. And then
this guy's like 6'5, you know, probably
250, 260. First time I saw him, I just
had a sick feeling in my stomach just
like, "NO, [laughter]
NO,
why can't he be like 5'1, buck 10 or
something?"
Some little step guy can toss around to
amuse the kids.
[laughter] That's a fun stepdad. The one
who lets you toss him around. Hey kids,
you want to see how I can tell your
stepdad today? It's funny, right? Get
over here.
Shouldn't matter. He's a good stepdad.
You know, he's nice to the kid. That's
all that's all that really matters. I
don't think about him being being
bigger, you know, a lot consciously, but
he's definitely snuck into my
subconscious.
>> [laughter]
>> cuz I'll be having weird daydreams.
He'll make a cameo, you know. I don't
even know why I'm really thinking about
it. I have thinking about some little
kid, you know, playground argument.
Like, yeah, my dad could beat up your
dad.
Maybe. I don't know.
He might not, you know, if I really
think about it, my stepdad could crush
your dad for sure.
My stepdad would destroy your dad. My
dad, he'd probably have something funny
to say about I don't know. Let's just
[laughter]
keep throwing a witty comment from a
safe distance.
Make up excuses later why he couldn't
join in. You know,
I think it's every dad wants to be the
alpha in the family. You know, like as a
guy you want to you want to be able to
protect the the kids. Like if god forbid
my kid stepdad ever, you know, did
something like smacked him around, I
would like to be able to smack him
around without even thinking about it,
you know? Just go just go knock him
around, see how he likes it. I want to
be that kind of dad. I don't want to be
the kind of dad. He's like, "What?" Your
stepdad hit you guys. Seriously, both of
you,
man. That's rough.
Bet that hurt. He's a big guy.
He probably hits pretty hard.
Not going to lie. You're in a tough
spot.
You're going to want to want to think
about what you did to upset him and
probably try and just do less of that.
[laughter]
Good luck.
For years, I tried to get these greeting
cards on storeshelves
and it just never worked. I don't know
why. I thought they were fun. I feel
like there's kind of, you know, meaner
cards out there now, which is more my
sense of humor, but maybe maybe they
just weren't ready for them. I had fun
stuff like, "Happy New Year's, buddy. I
made a resolution to hang out with
smarter, more attractive friends. You
take care of yourself."
[laughter]
I want to thank you for making me
believe again in the possibility of
Sasquatch. There's no way that thing's
entirely human. Congratulations on your
new baby.
[laughter]
As each day passes, you grow older and
weaker. I've been working out. Revenge
is near. Happy Father's Day. What
happened? You know, I I I have four
older brothers. Okay. Three of my older
brothers, super fun. Life of the party.
One of my older brothers,
kind of a hard ass.
bit of a bully.
When we were kids, he would beat us more
than our parents.
[laughter]
That's just wrong.
Now, guess which one of my brothers
became a cop?
So, I called him by accident. Do you
ever call the wrong sibling?
Hello. Like, oh,
now I got to think of something to say.
So, like, well, kids. He has kids. I
have kids. That we get that out of the
way. Five minutes. HEY, MAN. WHAT'S
GOING ON? Just uh checking in, seeing
what how you doing, you know. Uh just
got Nelly. That's my youngest daughter.
Just got Nelly your last set of
vaccinations, so she's all caught up.
Yeah, we're not going to be doing that
around here.
Going to keep our DNA intact.
[laughter]
>> Now, my brother knows my daughter is
adopted.
[laughter]
I have three daughters. They're all from
China
because I'm terrified of my DNA.
[laughter]
[applause]
AND I'M SORRY, I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW IT
CAN BE in this day and age that an
educated person can be against something
as fundamentally beneficial as a
vaccine.
And then it hit me.
You know why they're against it?
Cuz other people are for it.
The end.
That's it. [applause]
You just HAVE TO BE FOR something and
they'll show up. [laughter]
It's all they have. It's what they do.
Go online tomorrow morning and just
quietly post, "I like French toast.
[laughter]
Check back in 20 minutes."
French toast.
Breakfast of the privileged. What else
do YOU LIKE FOR BREAKFAST? GENOCIDE.
[laughter]
Where do you work?
But his reasoning drives me crazy. I
ain't getting vaccinated.
I don't know how it works,
[laughter]
right?
That's why we went out and got some
people smarter than you
so we can have fun stuff like open heart
surgery and airplanes.
[laughter]
I don't know how zippers work,
but every morning I put my faith in the
science,
[applause and cheering]
leave the house fairly certain I'm not
going to be in line at the bank with my
out.
[laughter]
It It all comes down to fear. It's just
fear.
I'm afraid I'm going to get sick. So, I
want everything you have. I want pills.
I want shots. I want surgery. I want
everything you can give me. But my
brother, he's much smarter than I am.
He's an independent thinker.
[laughter]
He thinks what all the other independent
thinkers think.
that the government,
the same people in charge of the post
office
[laughter]
and the DMV
are also behind a massive global genetic
super conspiracy
[laughter]
that I will believe when I can buy one
stamp in under 45 minutes. [laughter]